{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781933895","data":{"timestamp":" 946781933894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d4c0faf6-86a7-4a59-8614-fdaded0d3bff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_N_H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781940570","data":{"timestamp":" 946781940569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d4c0faf6-86a7-4a59-8614-fdaded0d3bff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_N_F"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781947235","data":{"timestamp":" 946781947234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d4c0faf6-86a7-4a59-8614-fdaded0d3bff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_O_E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781953891","data":{"timestamp":" 946781953891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d4c0faf6-86a7-4a59-8614-fdaded0d3bff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_P_Y"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781960529","data":{"timestamp":" 946781960529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d4c0faf6-86a7-4a59-8614-fdaded0d3bff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_F_R"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781967208","data":{"timestamp":" 946781967207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d4c0faf6-86a7-4a59-8614-fdaded0d3bff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_K_W_N"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781973877","data":{"timestamp":" 946781973877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d4c0faf6-86a7-4a59-8614-fdaded0d3bff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_N_P"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781980526","data":{"timestamp":" 946781980526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d4c0faf6-86a7-4a59-8614-fdaded0d3bff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_N_Y"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781987166","data":{"timestamp":" 946781987165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d4c0faf6-86a7-4a59-8614-fdaded0d3bff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_N_D"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781993872","data":{"timestamp":" 946781993872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d4c0faf6-86a7-4a59-8614-fdaded0d3bff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_N_G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782005986","data":{"timestamp":" 946782005985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d4c0faf6-86a7-4a59-8614-fdaded0d3bff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_Y_N_G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782031731","data":{"timestamp":" 946782031730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782032438","data":{"timestamp":" 946782032437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782032954","data":{"timestamp":" 946782032953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782033801","data":{"timestamp":" 946782033800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" JIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782034712","data":{"timestamp":" 946782034711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782034930","data":{"timestamp":" 946782034929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782035316","data":{"timestamp":" 946782035315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782036128","data":{"timestamp":" 946782036127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782038563","data":{"timestamp":" 946782038562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782039311","data":{"timestamp":" 946782039310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782040123","data":{"timestamp":" 946782040122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782040844","data":{"timestamp":" 946782040843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782041341","data":{"timestamp":" 946782041340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782041564","data":{"timestamp":" 946782041563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782042021","data":{"timestamp":" 946782042020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782042397","data":{"timestamp":" 946782042397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782045005","data":{"timestamp":" 946782045004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782045422","data":{"timestamp":" 946782045421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782046160","data":{"timestamp":" 946782046159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMII"," userResponse":" JAMII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782046270","data":{"timestamp":" 946782046270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782046888","data":{"timestamp":" 946782046888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINDI"," userResponse":" KINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782049216","data":{"timestamp":" 946782049215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKKI"," userResponse":" VIKKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782050074","data":{"timestamp":" 946782050073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782050676","data":{"timestamp":" 946782050676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782050853","data":{"timestamp":" 946782050853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782051536","data":{"timestamp":" 946782051535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINDI"," userResponse":" KINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782052500","data":{"timestamp":" 946782052500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIYEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782053224","data":{"timestamp":" 946782053224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONGEA"," userResponse":" KUONGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782053719","data":{"timestamp":" 946782053719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782054703","data":{"timestamp":" 946782054703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikki alikuwa mmoja wa kindi aliyependa kuongea mambo makubwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782057053","data":{"timestamp":" 946782057053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BINAMUYE"," userResponse":" BINAMUYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782057457","data":{"timestamp":" 946782057457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATO"," userResponse":" KATO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782058792","data":{"timestamp":" 946782058792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782059690","data":{"timestamp":" 946782059689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782059937","data":{"timestamp":" 946782059937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782060584","data":{"timestamp":" 946782060584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782061680","data":{"timestamp":" 946782061680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782062424","data":{"timestamp":" 946782062424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEKUJA"," userResponse":" AMEKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782063579","data":{"timestamp":" 946782063579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Binamuye Kato kutoka Msitu wa Mbali alikuwa amekuja kumtembelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTEMBELEA"," userResponse":" KUMTEMBELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782066489","data":{"timestamp":" 946782066488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782067032","data":{"timestamp":" 946782067031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782067977","data":{"timestamp":" 946782067976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782068574","data":{"timestamp":" 946782068573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782069582","data":{"timestamp":" 946782069582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOISHI"," userResponse":" WALIOISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782070189","data":{"timestamp":" 946782070188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782070583","data":{"timestamp":" 946782070583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782071267","data":{"timestamp":" 946782071266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782071743","data":{"timestamp":" 946782071743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782072926","data":{"timestamp":" 946782072926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782073728","data":{"timestamp":" 946782073728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wanyama wote walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo walienda kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782076107","data":{"timestamp":" 946782076106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782076914","data":{"timestamp":" 946782076914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISIKIA"," userResponse":" WALISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782077574","data":{"timestamp":" 946782077574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782078395","data":{"timestamp":" 946782078394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782079612","data":{"timestamp":" 946782079611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKA"," userResponse":" IKITOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782080241","data":{"timestamp":" 946782080240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782081081","data":{"timestamp":" 946782081080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782081760","data":{"timestamp":" 946782081759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara walisikia sauti kubwa ikitoka uwanja uliokuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782084674","data":{"timestamp":" 946782084674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATO"," userResponse":" KATO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782084870","data":{"timestamp":" 946782084870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782085631","data":{"timestamp":" 946782085630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINDI"," userResponse":" KINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782086592","data":{"timestamp":" 946782086591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782087618","data":{"timestamp":" 946782087617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782088358","data":{"timestamp":" 946782088358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHINE"," userResponse":" MASHINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782088950","data":{"timestamp":" 946782088950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782089139","data":{"timestamp":" 946782089139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782090030","data":{"timestamp":" 946782090029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato na kindi wengine waliona mashine kubwa ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782092633","data":{"timestamp":" 946782092632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782093232","data":{"timestamp":" 946782093232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782094205","data":{"timestamp":" 946782094204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782095363","data":{"timestamp":" 946782095362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOVALIA"," userResponse":" WALIOVALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782096094","data":{"timestamp":" 946782096094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782096705","data":{"timestamp":" 946782096704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUMU"," userResponse":" NGUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782097376","data":{"timestamp":" 946782097375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782098228","data":{"timestamp":" 946782098227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782099739","data":{"timestamp":" 946782099739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIONYESHA"," userResponse":" WAKIONYESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782100009","data":{"timestamp":" 946782100008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782100753","data":{"timestamp":" 946782100752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782101887","data":{"timestamp":" 946782101886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782102649","data":{"timestamp":" 946782102648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782103286","data":{"timestamp":" 946782103285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782103742","data":{"timestamp":" 946782103742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782104340","data":{"timestamp":" 946782104339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782105260","data":{"timestamp":" 946782105259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782106854","data":{"timestamp":" 946782106854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIZOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782107968","data":{"timestamp":" 946782107968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782108721","data":{"timestamp":" 946782108720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782108970","data":{"timestamp":" 946782108969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782109972","data":{"timestamp":" 946782109971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliona pia wanaume waliovalia kofia ngumu za manjano wakionyesha kwa vidole ile bustani ndogo na nyumba zingine zilizokuwa upande mwingine wa barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782112731","data":{"timestamp":" 946782112730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walinuia kuzivunja vunja zote kisha wajenge uwanja wa kuegesha magari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALINUIA"," userResponse":" WALINUIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782113702","data":{"timestamp":" 946782113701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walinuia kuzivunja vunja zote kisha wajenge uwanja wa kuegesha magari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZIVUNJA"," userResponse":" KUZIVUNJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782114485","data":{"timestamp":" 946782114485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walinuia kuzivunja vunja zote kisha wajenge uwanja wa kuegesha magari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VUNJA"," userResponse":" VUNJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782115194","data":{"timestamp":" 946782115194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walinuia kuzivunja vunja zote kisha wajenge uwanja wa kuegesha magari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782116095","data":{"timestamp":" 946782116095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walinuia kuzivunja vunja zote kisha wajenge uwanja wa kuegesha magari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782116878","data":{"timestamp":" 946782116877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walinuia kuzivunja vunja zote kisha wajenge uwanja wa kuegesha magari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAJENGE"," userResponse":" WAJENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782117719","data":{"timestamp":" 946782117718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walinuia kuzivunja vunja zote kisha wajenge uwanja wa kuegesha magari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782117948","data":{"timestamp":" 946782117947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walinuia kuzivunja vunja zote kisha wajenge uwanja wa kuegesha magari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782118898","data":{"timestamp":" 946782118898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walinuia kuzivunja vunja zote kisha wajenge uwanja wa kuegesha magari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUEGESHA"," userResponse":" KUEGESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782119518","data":{"timestamp":" 946782119517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walinuia kuzivunja vunja zote kisha wajenge uwanja wa kuegesha magari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" MAGARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782122415","data":{"timestamp":" 946782122414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walioishi pale wangehamia nyumba zingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782123353","data":{"timestamp":" 946782123352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walioishi pale wangehamia nyumba zingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOISHI"," userResponse":" WALIOISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782123954","data":{"timestamp":" 946782123954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walioishi pale wangehamia nyumba zingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782125570","data":{"timestamp":" 946782125570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walioishi pale wangehamia nyumba zingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEHAMIA"," userResponse":" WANGEHAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782126360","data":{"timestamp":" 946782126359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walioishi pale wangehamia nyumba zingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782127151","data":{"timestamp":" 946782127150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walioishi pale wangehamia nyumba zingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782129782","data":{"timestamp":" 946782129781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakuna aliyewafikiria wanyama ndege na wadudu walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782130486","data":{"timestamp":" 946782130485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakuna aliyewafikiria wanyama ndege na wadudu walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782132219","data":{"timestamp":" 946782132219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakuna aliyewafikiria wanyama ndege na wadudu walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEWAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ALIYEWAFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782132963","data":{"timestamp":" 946782132962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakuna aliyewafikiria wanyama ndege na wadudu walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782134066","data":{"timestamp":" 946782134066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakuna aliyewafikiria wanyama ndege na wadudu walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782134665","data":{"timestamp":" 946782134665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakuna aliyewafikiria wanyama ndege na wadudu walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782135142","data":{"timestamp":" 946782135141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakuna aliyewafikiria wanyama ndege na wadudu walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782136684","data":{"timestamp":" 946782136683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakuna aliyewafikiria wanyama ndege na wadudu walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOISHI"," userResponse":" WALIOISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782137263","data":{"timestamp":" 946782137263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakuna aliyewafikiria wanyama ndege na wadudu walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782137652","data":{"timestamp":" 946782137651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakuna aliyewafikiria wanyama ndege na wadudu walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782138334","data":{"timestamp":" 946782138333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakuna aliyewafikiria wanyama ndege na wadudu walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782138950","data":{"timestamp":" 946782138949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakuna aliyewafikiria wanyama ndege na wadudu walioishi katika ile bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782142106","data":{"timestamp":" 946782142105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHINE"," userResponse":" MASHINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782143094","data":{"timestamp":" 946782143093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIONWA"," userResponse":" ZILIONWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782144114","data":{"timestamp":" 946782144113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782144799","data":{"timestamp":" 946782144798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782145501","data":{"timestamp":" 946782145501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782145823","data":{"timestamp":" 946782145823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782146538","data":{"timestamp":" 946782146537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUGO"," userResponse":" FUGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782147539","data":{"timestamp":" 946782147539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782148042","data":{"timestamp":" 946782148041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782148882","data":{"timestamp":" 946782148882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POPPLES"," userResponse":" POPPLES"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782149996","data":{"timestamp":" 946782149996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782150537","data":{"timestamp":" 946782150537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782151096","data":{"timestamp":" 946782151095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782152324","data":{"timestamp":" 946782152322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYE"," userResponse":" AMBAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782153495","data":{"timestamp":" 946782153495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWELEZEA"," userResponse":" ALIMWELEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782153960","data":{"timestamp":" 946782153960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782154801","data":{"timestamp":" 946782154800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOPPLES"," userResponse":" MOPPLES"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782155917","data":{"timestamp":" 946782155916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782157070","data":{"timestamp":" 946782157069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWELEZEA"," userResponse":" AKAMWELEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782157465","data":{"timestamp":" 946782157464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782158204","data":{"timestamp":" 946782158203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782159478","data":{"timestamp":" 946782159478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POPPLES"," userResponse":" POPPLES"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782160182","data":{"timestamp":" 946782160182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mashine zilionwa kwanza na familia ya fugo hasa Bwana Popples mkubwa kwa umri ambaye alimwelezea Bwana Mopples naye akamwelezea mdogo wao Popples Mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782163379","data":{"timestamp":" 946782163378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wachanga waliitwa Pop Mop na Pip."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782164137","data":{"timestamp":" 946782164137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wachanga waliitwa Pop Mop na Pip."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHANGA"," userResponse":" WACHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782165377","data":{"timestamp":" 946782165376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wachanga waliitwa Pop Mop na Pip."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIITWA"," userResponse":" WALIITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782165893","data":{"timestamp":" 946782165892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wachanga waliitwa Pop Mop na Pip."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POP"," userResponse":" POP"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782166866","data":{"timestamp":" 946782166866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wachanga waliitwa Pop Mop na Pip."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOP"," userResponse":" MOP"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782167404","data":{"timestamp":" 946782167404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wachanga waliitwa Pop Mop na Pip."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782168274","data":{"timestamp":" 946782168273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wachanga waliitwa Pop Mop na Pip."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIP"," userResponse":" PIP"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782170634","data":{"timestamp":" 946782170633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782171411","data":{"timestamp":" 946782171410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POPPLES"," userResponse":" POPPLES"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782172554","data":{"timestamp":" 946782172554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIWAAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782173314","data":{"timestamp":" 946782173313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINDI"," userResponse":" KINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782174285","data":{"timestamp":" 946782174284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINDI"," userResponse":" KINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782175767","data":{"timestamp":" 946782175766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" WAKAWAAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782176459","data":{"timestamp":" 946782176459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782177491","data":{"timestamp":" 946782177491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782177729","data":{"timestamp":" 946782177729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782178853","data":{"timestamp":" 946782178853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782180684","data":{"timestamp":" 946782180683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782182025","data":{"timestamp":" 946782182025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782182758","data":{"timestamp":" 946782182758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782183357","data":{"timestamp":" 946782183356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782183908","data":{"timestamp":" 946782183907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782184804","data":{"timestamp":" 946782184803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782185747","data":{"timestamp":" 946782185747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOISHI"," userResponse":" WALIOISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782186363","data":{"timestamp":" 946782186362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782187210","data":{"timestamp":" 946782187209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782187635","data":{"timestamp":" 946782187635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782188447","data":{"timestamp":" 946782188447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliwaambia kindi kindi wakawaambia ndege watoto wa vipepeo vipepeo buibui wadogo mno na wote walioishi katika bustani ile ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782191092","data":{"timestamp":" 946782191091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKIWA"," userResponse":" KULIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782191362","data":{"timestamp":" 946782191361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782192440","data":{"timestamp":" 946782192439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VURUMAI"," userResponse":" VURUMAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782194075","data":{"timestamp":" 946782194074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782194814","data":{"timestamp":" 946782194813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWINGI"," userResponse":" KWINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782196076","data":{"timestamp":" 946782196074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782196429","data":{"timestamp":" 946782196429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782196499","data":{"timestamp":" 946782196499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782197224","data":{"timestamp":" 946782197223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKO"," userResponse":" HUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782198198","data":{"timestamp":" 946782198197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782198896","data":{"timestamp":" 946782198895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYOTE"," userResponse":" YEYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782199541","data":{"timestamp":" 946782199541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJUA"," userResponse":" KUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782199771","data":{"timestamp":" 946782199770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782200552","data":{"timestamp":" 946782200552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782202926","data":{"timestamp":" 946782202925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782203281","data":{"timestamp":" 946782203281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782204218","data":{"timestamp":" 946782204217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi kwa kwenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782207412","data":{"timestamp":" 946782207411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vipepeo wakasema Tunataka maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782207608","data":{"timestamp":" 946782207607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vipepeo wakasema Tunataka maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782208399","data":{"timestamp":" 946782208399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vipepeo wakasema Tunataka maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782209410","data":{"timestamp":" 946782209410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vipepeo wakasema Tunataka maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISEMA"," userResponse":" WALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782210432","data":{"timestamp":" 946782210431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vipepeo wakasema Tunataka maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782211464","data":{"timestamp":" 946782211464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vipepeo wakasema Tunataka maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAFUTE"," userResponse":" TUTAFUTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782212376","data":{"timestamp":" 946782212375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vipepeo wakasema Tunataka maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782215064","data":{"timestamp":" 946782215064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vipepeo wakasema Tunataka maua."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782216067","data":{"timestamp":" 946782216066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vipepeo wakasema Tunataka maua."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKASEMA"," userResponse":" WAKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782217407","data":{"timestamp":" 946782217406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vipepeo wakasema Tunataka maua."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNATAKA"," userResponse":" TUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782218128","data":{"timestamp":" 946782218127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vipepeo wakasema Tunataka maua."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782220445","data":{"timestamp":" 946782220445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo walitaka kujilimia mashimo yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782220853","data":{"timestamp":" 946782220852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo walitaka kujilimia mashimo yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782221945","data":{"timestamp":" 946782221945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo walitaka kujilimia mashimo yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" WALITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782222646","data":{"timestamp":" 946782222645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo walitaka kujilimia mashimo yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHIMO"," userResponse":" MASHIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782225190","data":{"timestamp":" 946782225189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo walitaka kujilimia mashimo yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUGO"," userResponse":" FUGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782225990","data":{"timestamp":" 946782225989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo walitaka kujilimia mashimo yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" WALITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782227122","data":{"timestamp":" 946782227121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo walitaka kujilimia mashimo yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJILIMIA"," userResponse":" KUJILIMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782227796","data":{"timestamp":" 946782227796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo walitaka kujilimia mashimo yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHIMO"," userResponse":" MASHIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782228254","data":{"timestamp":" 946782228254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo walitaka kujilimia mashimo yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782230976","data":{"timestamp":" 946782230975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kindi ndege na wadudu walitaka miti vichaka na nyasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINDI"," userResponse":" KINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782231971","data":{"timestamp":" 946782231967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kindi ndege na wadudu walitaka miti vichaka na nyasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782232522","data":{"timestamp":" 946782232521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kindi ndege na wadudu walitaka miti vichaka na nyasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782233360","data":{"timestamp":" 946782233359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kindi ndege na wadudu walitaka miti vichaka na nyasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782234494","data":{"timestamp":" 946782234492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kindi ndege na wadudu walitaka miti vichaka na nyasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" WALITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782235235","data":{"timestamp":" 946782235234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kindi ndege na wadudu walitaka miti vichaka na nyasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782236277","data":{"timestamp":" 946782236276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kindi ndege na wadudu walitaka miti vichaka na nyasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHAKA"," userResponse":" VICHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782236781","data":{"timestamp":" 946782236776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kindi ndege na wadudu walitaka miti vichaka na nyasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782237404","data":{"timestamp":" 946782237403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kindi ndege na wadudu walitaka miti vichaka na nyasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782239759","data":{"timestamp":" 946782239758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782240447","data":{"timestamp":" 946782240447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782241219","data":{"timestamp":" 946782241218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" WALITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782241892","data":{"timestamp":" 946782241891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782242947","data":{"timestamp":" 946782242946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYORORO"," userResponse":" NYORORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782243167","data":{"timestamp":" 946782243167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782243841","data":{"timestamp":" 946782243841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782244655","data":{"timestamp":" 946782244655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782244998","data":{"timestamp":" 946782244997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782245711","data":{"timestamp":" 946782245710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782245935","data":{"timestamp":" 946782245935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782246698","data":{"timestamp":" 946782246697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMITI"," userResponse":" SIMITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782247019","data":{"timestamp":" 946782247019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782247966","data":{"timestamp":" 946782247965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARUJI"," userResponse":" SARUJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782250072","data":{"timestamp":" 946782250071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782250662","data":{"timestamp":" 946782250661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782251523","data":{"timestamp":" 946782251522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAPATA"," userResponse":" TUTAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782252012","data":{"timestamp":" 946782252011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782252867","data":{"timestamp":" 946782252866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782255192","data":{"timestamp":" 946782255191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782255871","data":{"timestamp":" 946782255870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782257046","data":{"timestamp":" 946782257044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKUFA"," userResponse":" TUTAKUFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782258436","data":{"timestamp":" 946782258435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISEMA"," userResponse":" WALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782259356","data":{"timestamp":" 946782259356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782260652","data":{"timestamp":" 946782260651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKALIA"," userResponse":" WAKALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782260954","data":{"timestamp":" 946782260953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782261638","data":{"timestamp":" 946782261637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" UCHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782265679","data":{"timestamp":" 946782265679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBAKE"," userResponse":" MJOMBAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782266126","data":{"timestamp":" 946782266125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATO"," userResponse":" KATO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782266552","data":{"timestamp":" 946782266552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782267603","data":{"timestamp":" 946782267602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" SHANGAZIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782268902","data":{"timestamp":" 946782268901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782269833","data":{"timestamp":" 946782269833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782270425","data":{"timestamp":" 946782270424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782270965","data":{"timestamp":" 946782270964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782271445","data":{"timestamp":" 946782271445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINDI"," userResponse":" KINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782271926","data":{"timestamp":" 946782271925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782272650","data":{"timestamp":" 946782272650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782273844","data":{"timestamp":" 946782273844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISONGA"," userResponse":" WALISONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782274487","data":{"timestamp":" 946782274487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782274706","data":{"timestamp":" 946782274705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782275469","data":{"timestamp":" 946782275468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mjombake Kato na shangaziye walikuwa kimya sana na kindi wote wadogo walisonga karibu na mamao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAO"," userResponse":" MAMAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782278222","data":{"timestamp":" 946782278221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATO"," userResponse":" KATO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782279241","data":{"timestamp":" 946782279240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISAFISHA"," userResponse":" ALISAFISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782279903","data":{"timestamp":" 946782279903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOO"," userResponse":" KOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782280548","data":{"timestamp":" 946782280548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782281209","data":{"timestamp":" 946782281208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782282073","data":{"timestamp":" 946782282072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONGEA"," userResponse":" KUONGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782282510","data":{"timestamp":" 946782282510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782283345","data":{"timestamp":" 946782283344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIONA"," userResponse":" AKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782283855","data":{"timestamp":" 946782283855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782285130","data":{"timestamp":" 946782285130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAISHI"," userResponse":" NAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782285812","data":{"timestamp":" 946782285812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782286365","data":{"timestamp":" 946782286364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782286725","data":{"timestamp":" 946782286725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782287389","data":{"timestamp":" 946782287388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782288392","data":{"timestamp":" 946782288392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782289237","data":{"timestamp":" 946782289236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782289779","data":{"timestamp":" 946782289778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782290395","data":{"timestamp":" 946782290394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782290908","data":{"timestamp":" 946782290908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alisafisha koo na kuanza kuongea huku akiona haya Naishi katika Msitu wa Mbali labda tunaweza kwenda sote huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKO"," userResponse":" HUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782293207","data":{"timestamp":" 946782293207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na sauti za mchangamko na mmoja akasema Vipi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782293423","data":{"timestamp":" 946782293422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na sauti za mchangamko na mmoja akasema Vipi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782294175","data":{"timestamp":" 946782294175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na sauti za mchangamko na mmoja akasema Vipi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782294393","data":{"timestamp":" 946782294392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na sauti za mchangamko na mmoja akasema Vipi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782295774","data":{"timestamp":" 946782295772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na sauti za mchangamko na mmoja akasema Vipi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANGAMKO"," userResponse":" MCHANGAMKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782296405","data":{"timestamp":" 946782296405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na sauti za mchangamko na mmoja akasema Vipi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782297068","data":{"timestamp":" 946782297068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na sauti za mchangamko na mmoja akasema Vipi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782297973","data":{"timestamp":" 946782297972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na sauti za mchangamko na mmoja akasema Vipi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782299495","data":{"timestamp":" 946782299495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na sauti za mchangamko na mmoja akasema Vipi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPI"," userResponse":" VIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782302458","data":{"timestamp":" 946782302458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATO"," userResponse":" KATO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782303319","data":{"timestamp":" 946782303319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUNA"," userResponse":" ALIKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782304011","data":{"timestamp":" 946782304010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782304509","data":{"timestamp":" 946782304508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782305161","data":{"timestamp":" 946782305161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAZA"," userResponse":" KUWAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782305690","data":{"timestamp":" 946782305684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782306944","data":{"timestamp":" 946782306943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782308435","data":{"timestamp":" 946782308435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINDI"," userResponse":" KINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782308580","data":{"timestamp":" 946782308580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782309090","data":{"timestamp":" 946782309090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782309362","data":{"timestamp":" 946782309362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782309903","data":{"timestamp":" 946782309903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782311094","data":{"timestamp":" 946782311093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAWEZA"," userResponse":" INAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782311948","data":{"timestamp":" 946782311947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782312651","data":{"timestamp":" 946782312651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINDI"," userResponse":" KINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782313093","data":{"timestamp":" 946782313092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782314121","data":{"timestamp":" 946782314120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782315578","data":{"timestamp":" 946782315578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782316735","data":{"timestamp":" 946782316734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782316945","data":{"timestamp":" 946782316944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782317932","data":{"timestamp":" 946782317932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782318604","data":{"timestamp":" 946782318603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782319316","data":{"timestamp":" 946782319315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782320095","data":{"timestamp":" 946782320094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kato alikuna kichwa na kuwaza sana Sawa Kindi ya Moja kwa Moja inaweza kuwapeleka kindi na vipepeo buibui watoto wa vipepeo na wadudu wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 23"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782322210","data":{"timestamp":" 946782322209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wanaweza kuruka au waje nasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782323060","data":{"timestamp":" 946782323059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wanaweza kuruka au waje nasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWEZA"," userResponse":" WANAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782323996","data":{"timestamp":" 946782323995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wanaweza kuruka au waje nasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782324539","data":{"timestamp":" 946782324539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wanaweza kuruka au waje nasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782325104","data":{"timestamp":" 946782325104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wanaweza kuruka au waje nasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAJE"," userResponse":" WAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782325588","data":{"timestamp":" 946782325588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wanaweza kuruka au waje nasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASI"," userResponse":" NASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782328071","data":{"timestamp":" 946782328071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUGO"," userResponse":" FUGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782328530","data":{"timestamp":" 946782328529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAO"," userResponse":" NAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782329228","data":{"timestamp":" 946782329228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782329437","data":{"timestamp":" 946782329436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782330177","data":{"timestamp":" 946782330177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782330983","data":{"timestamp":" 946782330982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782331482","data":{"timestamp":" 946782331481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782332123","data":{"timestamp":" 946782332123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782332322","data":{"timestamp":" 946782332321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782333164","data":{"timestamp":" 946782333163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASINI"," userResponse":" NYASINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782334236","data":{"timestamp":" 946782334236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWEZA"," userResponse":" WANAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782335140","data":{"timestamp":" 946782335140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782335704","data":{"timestamp":" 946782335703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUGO"," userResponse":" FUGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782335926","data":{"timestamp":" 946782335926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782336419","data":{"timestamp":" 946782336419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782336693","data":{"timestamp":" 946782336692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782337200","data":{"timestamp":" 946782337199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782338624","data":{"timestamp":" 946782338624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IPITIAYO"," userResponse":" IPITIAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782339389","data":{"timestamp":" 946782339388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782339665","data":{"timestamp":" 946782339664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782340261","data":{"timestamp":" 946782340260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fugo nao pamoja na panya wadogo na nyoka wa nyasini wanaweza kutumia Fugo ya Moja kwa Moja ipitiayo chini kwa chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782342295","data":{"timestamp":" 946782342294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alifikiria kuwa hilo lilikuwa wazo murua kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782342995","data":{"timestamp":" 946782342994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alifikiria kuwa hilo lilikuwa wazo murua kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782344259","data":{"timestamp":" 946782344259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alifikiria kuwa hilo lilikuwa wazo murua kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782344707","data":{"timestamp":" 946782344706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alifikiria kuwa hilo lilikuwa wazo murua kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782345134","data":{"timestamp":" 946782345133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alifikiria kuwa hilo lilikuwa wazo murua kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782345978","data":{"timestamp":" 946782345977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alifikiria kuwa hilo lilikuwa wazo murua kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782347109","data":{"timestamp":" 946782347108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alifikiria kuwa hilo lilikuwa wazo murua kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782348037","data":{"timestamp":" 946782348037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alifikiria kuwa hilo lilikuwa wazo murua kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MURUA"," userResponse":" MURUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782349179","data":{"timestamp":" 946782349178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alifikiria kuwa hilo lilikuwa wazo murua kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782351951","data":{"timestamp":" 946782351950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782352733","data":{"timestamp":" 946782352732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POPPLES"," userResponse":" POPPLES"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782354283","data":{"timestamp":" 946782354283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" ALIHARAKISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782355352","data":{"timestamp":" 946782355351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUULIZA"," userResponse":" KUMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782355795","data":{"timestamp":" 946782355794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782356638","data":{"timestamp":" 946782356637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRUMBLES"," userResponse":" GRUMBLES"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782357909","data":{"timestamp":" 946782357909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782358100","data":{"timestamp":" 946782358100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782358967","data":{"timestamp":" 946782358965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782359108","data":{"timestamp":" 946782359107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782359653","data":{"timestamp":" 946782359653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782359908","data":{"timestamp":" 946782359908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782360433","data":{"timestamp":" 946782360433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782360748","data":{"timestamp":" 946782360748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782361353","data":{"timestamp":" 946782361353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782361623","data":{"timestamp":" 946782361623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782362309","data":{"timestamp":" 946782362308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782363373","data":{"timestamp":" 946782363373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782364188","data":{"timestamp":" 946782364188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZA"," userResponse":" ANGEWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782364995","data":{"timestamp":" 946782364995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWABEBA"," userResponse":" KUWABEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782365712","data":{"timestamp":" 946782365712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782366623","data":{"timestamp":" 946782366622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782367098","data":{"timestamp":" 946782367097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782367562","data":{"timestamp":" 946782367562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 23"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782368397","data":{"timestamp":" 946782368397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Popples aliharakisha kumuuliza Bwana Grumbles dereva wa treni ya moja kwa moja ya chini kwa chini ikiwa angeweza kuwabeba wote hadi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 24"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782370298","data":{"timestamp":" 946782370297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Grumbles alibabaika akagugumia kabla ya kusema Sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782371080","data":{"timestamp":" 946782371080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Grumbles alibabaika akagugumia kabla ya kusema Sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRUMBLES"," userResponse":" GRUMBLES"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782372340","data":{"timestamp":" 946782372339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Grumbles alibabaika akagugumia kabla ya kusema Sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIBABAIKA"," userResponse":" ALIBABAIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782374115","data":{"timestamp":" 946782374115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Grumbles alibabaika akagugumia kabla ya kusema Sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAGUGUMIA"," userResponse":" AKAGUGUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782374939","data":{"timestamp":" 946782374939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Grumbles alibabaika akagugumia kabla ya kusema Sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782375113","data":{"timestamp":" 946782375113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Grumbles alibabaika akagugumia kabla ya kusema Sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782375786","data":{"timestamp":" 946782375785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Grumbles alibabaika akagugumia kabla ya kusema Sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782377308","data":{"timestamp":" 946782377307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Grumbles alibabaika akagugumia kabla ya kusema Sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782379738","data":{"timestamp":" 946782379737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilikuwa zamu ya Bwana Popples kuwa mwungwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782380618","data":{"timestamp":" 946782380617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilikuwa zamu ya Bwana Popples kuwa mwungwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782381170","data":{"timestamp":" 946782381170"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilikuwa zamu ya Bwana Popples kuwa mwungwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMU"," userResponse":" ZAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782381400","data":{"timestamp":" 946782381399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilikuwa zamu ya Bwana Popples kuwa mwungwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782381825","data":{"timestamp":" 946782381824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilikuwa zamu ya Bwana Popples kuwa mwungwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782382526","data":{"timestamp":" 946782382525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilikuwa zamu ya Bwana Popples kuwa mwungwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POPPLES"," userResponse":" POPPLES"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782383005","data":{"timestamp":" 946782383004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilikuwa zamu ya Bwana Popples kuwa mwungwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782384016","data":{"timestamp":" 946782384016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilikuwa zamu ya Bwana Popples kuwa mwungwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWUNGWANA"," userResponse":" MWUNGWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782387071","data":{"timestamp":" 946782387070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782387924","data":{"timestamp":" 946782387923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMNA"," userResponse":" HAMNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782388455","data":{"timestamp":" 946782388454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAJA"," userResponse":" HAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782388724","data":{"timestamp":" 946782388723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782389189","data":{"timestamp":" 946782389188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782389420","data":{"timestamp":" 946782389420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782390520","data":{"timestamp":" 946782390520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" WASIWASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782391612","data":{"timestamp":" 946782391612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782391929","data":{"timestamp":" 946782391929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782392388","data":{"timestamp":" 946782392388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPWA"," userResponse":" MPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782392588","data":{"timestamp":" 946782392588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782393589","data":{"timestamp":" 946782393588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782395747","data":{"timestamp":" 946782395747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782396306","data":{"timestamp":" 946782396305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPWA"," userResponse":" MPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782396534","data":{"timestamp":" 946782396534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782397592","data":{"timestamp":" 946782397592"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUKUU"," userResponse":" MJUKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782399817","data":{"timestamp":" 946782399817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782400286","data":{"timestamp":" 946782400285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" BABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782401231","data":{"timestamp":" 946782401230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782403993","data":{"timestamp":" 946782403992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAISHI"," userResponse":" INAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782404625","data":{"timestamp":" 946782404624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782404841","data":{"timestamp":" 946782404840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782405482","data":{"timestamp":" 946782405481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inaishi Msitu wa Mbali."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782408172","data":{"timestamp":" 946782408172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782409120","data":{"timestamp":" 946782409119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782410161","data":{"timestamp":" 946782410161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782410389","data":{"timestamp":" 946782410389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782410973","data":{"timestamp":" 946782410973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782411166","data":{"timestamp":" 946782411166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782412291","data":{"timestamp":" 946782412290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782413266","data":{"timestamp":" 946782413266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINDI"," userResponse":" KINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782413820","data":{"timestamp":" 946782413819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782414100","data":{"timestamp":" 946782414100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782414704","data":{"timestamp":" 946782414703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782415235","data":{"timestamp":" 946782415235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782415997","data":{"timestamp":" 946782415997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782416605","data":{"timestamp":" 946782416605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AINA"," userResponse":" AINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782416916","data":{"timestamp":" 946782416915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782417577","data":{"timestamp":" 946782417577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUGO"," userResponse":" FUGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782418053","data":{"timestamp":" 946782418052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782418552","data":{"timestamp":" 946782418552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782418798","data":{"timestamp":" 946782418798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782419552","data":{"timestamp":" 946782419551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782420620","data":{"timestamp":" 946782420620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782420825","data":{"timestamp":" 946782420825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782421598","data":{"timestamp":" 946782421597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782422298","data":{"timestamp":" 946782422298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 23"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782423774","data":{"timestamp":" 946782423773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 24"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIENDESHA"," userResponse":" ILIENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782424648","data":{"timestamp":" 946782424648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 25"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782425174","data":{"timestamp":" 946782425174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 26"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782425857","data":{"timestamp":" 946782425857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 27"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782426869","data":{"timestamp":" 946782426869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 28"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUELEKEA"," userResponse":" KUELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782427537","data":{"timestamp":" 946782427536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 29"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782427805","data":{"timestamp":" 946782427805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 30"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782428522","data":{"timestamp":" 946782428522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 31"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782429565","data":{"timestamp":" 946782429564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 32"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIO"," userResponse":" ULIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782429829","data":{"timestamp":" 946782429829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 33"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782430652","data":{"timestamp":" 946782430651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 34"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782432053","data":{"timestamp":" 946782432053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 35"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782433382","data":{"timestamp":" 946782433382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 36"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDIMBWI"," userResponse":" VIDIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782434089","data":{"timestamp":" 946782434089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 37"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782434800","data":{"timestamp":" 946782434800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 38"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782435733","data":{"timestamp":" 946782435733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 39"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYORORO"," userResponse":" NYORORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_49__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782465621","data":{"timestamp":" 946782465619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782465746","data":{"timestamp":" 946782465746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 21b147c0-5dd5-4c90-8f7e-493afdb47932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_49__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo wakati wa saa za asubuhi Kindi Moja kwa Moja na treni aina ya Fugo ya chini kwa chini pamoja na abiria wote iliendesha safari yake ya kuelekea Msitu wa Mbali ulio na miti maua vidimbwi na ardhi nyororo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 39"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYORORO"," userResponse":" NYORORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782516111","data":{"timestamp":" 946782516110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782516344","data":{"timestamp":" 946782516344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782517321","data":{"timestamp":" 946782517320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782518609","data":{"timestamp":" 946782518609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782521550","data":{"timestamp":" 946782521550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782522396","data":{"timestamp":" 946782522395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782522716","data":{"timestamp":" 946782522715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782523964","data":{"timestamp":" 946782523963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782527518","data":{"timestamp":" 946782527517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782528513","data":{"timestamp":" 946782528512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782528777","data":{"timestamp":" 946782528776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782529733","data":{"timestamp":" 946782529733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782532650","data":{"timestamp":" 946782532650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782533692","data":{"timestamp":" 946782533692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782534172","data":{"timestamp":" 946782534172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782538748","data":{"timestamp":" 946782538746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782538881","data":{"timestamp":" 946782538881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" d28020a9-49ed-4079-abf1-0cd591e1b8ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_14"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782583304","data":{"timestamp":" 946782583303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782583919","data":{"timestamp":" 946782583919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782584154","data":{"timestamp":" 946782584153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782584763","data":{"timestamp":" 946782584763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782585537","data":{"timestamp":" 946782585536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIA"," userResponse":" DUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782586536","data":{"timestamp":" 946782586535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782587185","data":{"timestamp":" 946782587183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782588377","data":{"timestamp":" 946782588377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" MILIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782589128","data":{"timestamp":" 946782589128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUBWA"," userResponse":" MIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782590380","data":{"timestamp":" 946782590379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIFUNIKA"," userResponse":" ILIFUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782591200","data":{"timestamp":" 946782591200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMWENGU"," userResponse":" ULIMWENGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782591688","data":{"timestamp":" 946782591687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782592617","data":{"timestamp":" 946782592616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" BLANKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782594906","data":{"timestamp":" 946782594905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782595393","data":{"timestamp":" 946782595393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782596126","data":{"timestamp":" 946782596126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIREFU"," userResponse":" MIREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782597348","data":{"timestamp":" 946782597348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILICHONGOKA"," userResponse":" ILICHONGOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782598452","data":{"timestamp":" 946782598452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGUNI"," userResponse":" MAWINGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782601808","data":{"timestamp":" 946782601807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIANI"," userResponse":" DUNIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782602666","data":{"timestamp":" 946782602665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782602934","data":{"timestamp":" 946782602934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782603513","data":{"timestamp":" 946782603512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782604058","data":{"timestamp":" 946782604057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782604289","data":{"timestamp":" 946782604288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782604869","data":{"timestamp":" 946782604868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782605702","data":{"timestamp":" 946782605701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782606644","data":{"timestamp":" 946782606643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHADIDI"," userResponse":" SHADIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782606884","data":{"timestamp":" 946782606883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782608241","data":{"timestamp":" 946782608241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOTULIA"," userResponse":" LILILOTULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782609225","data":{"timestamp":" 946782609224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULI"," userResponse":" TULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782611464","data":{"timestamp":" 946782611463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782612129","data":{"timestamp":" 946782612129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782612950","data":{"timestamp":" 946782612949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782614019","data":{"timestamp":" 946782614018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIREFU"," userResponse":" KIREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782614747","data":{"timestamp":" 946782614746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782615961","data":{"timestamp":" 946782615961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIGUBIKWA"," userResponse":" LILIGUBIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782616165","data":{"timestamp":" 946782616165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782616679","data":{"timestamp":" 946782616679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782617673","data":{"timestamp":" 946782617673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOTORO"," userResponse":" TOTORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782620645","data":{"timestamp":" 946782620644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782621612","data":{"timestamp":" 946782621611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKAFU"," userResponse":" SAKAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782621900","data":{"timestamp":" 946782621899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782622657","data":{"timestamp":" 946782622656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782623301","data":{"timestamp":" 946782623301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782624273","data":{"timestamp":" 946782624271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782625132","data":{"timestamp":" 946782625131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782625699","data":{"timestamp":" 946782625698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782628252","data":{"timestamp":" 946782628252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782629169","data":{"timestamp":" 946782629168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782630127","data":{"timestamp":" 946782630126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNENE"," userResponse":" MNENE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782630801","data":{"timestamp":" 946782630800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782631328","data":{"timestamp":" 946782631328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782631918","data":{"timestamp":" 946782631917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782634120","data":{"timestamp":" 946782634119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782635000","data":{"timestamp":" 946782635000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENGINE"," userResponse":" MWENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782636011","data":{"timestamp":" 946782636010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782636278","data":{"timestamp":" 946782636277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782636803","data":{"timestamp":" 946782636803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBO"," userResponse":" UMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782637574","data":{"timestamp":" 946782637574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOGO"," userResponse":" DOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782637731","data":{"timestamp":" 946782637731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782638814","data":{"timestamp":" 946782638814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTIA"," userResponse":" KUVUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782639372","data":{"timestamp":" 946782639372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782640087","data":{"timestamp":" 946782640087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHAIFU"," userResponse":" DHAIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782643148","data":{"timestamp":" 946782643148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782643886","data":{"timestamp":" 946782643885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782644404","data":{"timestamp":" 946782644403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782645516","data":{"timestamp":" 946782645515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKATOKEA"," userResponse":" PAKATOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782646450","data":{"timestamp":" 946782646449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHORUBA"," userResponse":" DHORUBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782647059","data":{"timestamp":" 946782647059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782649666","data":{"timestamp":" 946782649666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADI"," userResponse":" RADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782650524","data":{"timestamp":" 946782650522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPIGA"," userResponse":" ILIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782650741","data":{"timestamp":" 946782650741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782651502","data":{"timestamp":" 946782651502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENYA"," userResponse":" KUPENYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782652061","data":{"timestamp":" 946782652060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782652670","data":{"timestamp":" 946782652670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782652883","data":{"timestamp":" 946782652882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782653518","data":{"timestamp":" 946782653517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782656095","data":{"timestamp":" 946782656094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782657285","data":{"timestamp":" 946782657285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAGAWIKA"," userResponse":" YAKAGAWIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782657594","data":{"timestamp":" 946782657593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782658058","data":{"timestamp":" 946782658058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782658772","data":{"timestamp":" 946782658772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782659585","data":{"timestamp":" 946782659585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782660160","data":{"timestamp":" 946782660160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782660944","data":{"timestamp":" 946782660944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAWEZA"," userResponse":" WAKAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782661548","data":{"timestamp":" 946782661548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782662173","data":{"timestamp":" 946782662173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782662807","data":{"timestamp":" 946782662807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782663442","data":{"timestamp":" 946782663442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782666280","data":{"timestamp":" 946782666279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782666827","data":{"timestamp":" 946782666827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITU"," userResponse":" VITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782667146","data":{"timestamp":" 946782667145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782667787","data":{"timestamp":" 946782667786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782668438","data":{"timestamp":" 946782668437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782668696","data":{"timestamp":" 946782668695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782669268","data":{"timestamp":" 946782669267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYENYE"," userResponse":" VYENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782669990","data":{"timestamp":" 946782669989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUMBO"," userResponse":" MAUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782670973","data":{"timestamp":" 946782670972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782672035","data":{"timestamp":" 946782672035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782674728","data":{"timestamp":" 946782674727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782675644","data":{"timestamp":" 946782675642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" VIUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782676226","data":{"timestamp":" 946782676225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782676836","data":{"timestamp":" 946782676836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782677718","data":{"timestamp":" 946782677717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782679994","data":{"timestamp":" 946782679993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782680539","data":{"timestamp":" 946782680539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782681827","data":{"timestamp":" 946782681826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHOONA"," userResponse":" WALICHOONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782682671","data":{"timestamp":" 946782682670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHINI"," userResponse":" ARDHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782683850","data":{"timestamp":" 946782683850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIVUTIA"," userResponse":" KILIVUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782684439","data":{"timestamp":" 946782684439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782686924","data":{"timestamp":" 946782686923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782687384","data":{"timestamp":" 946782687383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782688830","data":{"timestamp":" 946782688826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIPORUDIANA"," userResponse":" YALIPORUDIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782689416","data":{"timestamp":" 946782689416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782690283","data":{"timestamp":" 946782690282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782690852","data":{"timestamp":" 946782690852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782692099","data":{"timestamp":" 946782692099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDELEA"," userResponse":" WALIENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782693200","data":{"timestamp":" 946782693200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" KUKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782693971","data":{"timestamp":" 946782693971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZURI"," userResponse":" UZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782695034","data":{"timestamp":" 946782695033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782695947","data":{"timestamp":" 946782695946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEONA"," userResponse":" WAMEONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782699311","data":{"timestamp":" 946782699310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUWEZI"," userResponse":" HATUWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782700269","data":{"timestamp":" 946782700268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUENDELEA"," userResponse":" KUENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782700969","data":{"timestamp":" 946782700968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782701405","data":{"timestamp":" 946782701404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782701952","data":{"timestamp":" 946782701952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782702383","data":{"timestamp":" 946782702382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782702813","data":{"timestamp":" 946782702813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LENYE"," userResponse":" LENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782703520","data":{"timestamp":" 946782703519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782703809","data":{"timestamp":" 946782703808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782704916","data":{"timestamp":" 946782704916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782706478","data":{"timestamp":" 946782706477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMBIANA"," userResponse":" WALIAMBIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782708768","data":{"timestamp":" 946782708767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782709192","data":{"timestamp":" 946782709191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782709637","data":{"timestamp":" 946782709637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782710668","data":{"timestamp":" 946782710667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKAIONE"," userResponse":" TUKAIONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782711458","data":{"timestamp":" 946782711457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782714586","data":{"timestamp":" 946782714585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAWEZAJE"," userResponse":" TUTAWEZAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782715220","data":{"timestamp":" 946782715219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782715767","data":{"timestamp":" 946782715766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782716620","data":{"timestamp":" 946782716620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782718835","data":{"timestamp":" 946782718835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782719248","data":{"timestamp":" 946782719248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782719881","data":{"timestamp":" 946782719881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782720965","data":{"timestamp":" 946782720965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782723188","data":{"timestamp":" 946782723188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782724977","data":{"timestamp":" 946782724976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTATAMBAA"," userResponse":" TUTATAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782725261","data":{"timestamp":" 946782725261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782726299","data":{"timestamp":" 946782726298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUMBO"," userResponse":" MATUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782729119","data":{"timestamp":" 946782729118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782729291","data":{"timestamp":" 946782729291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782730136","data":{"timestamp":" 946782730136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782731577","data":{"timestamp":" 946782731576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWATATUCHEKA"," userResponse":" HAWATATUCHEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782731788","data":{"timestamp":" 946782731787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782732695","data":{"timestamp":" 946782732695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUONA"," userResponse":" KUTUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782733331","data":{"timestamp":" 946782733331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNI"," userResponse":" DUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782734510","data":{"timestamp":" 946782734509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENZAKE"," userResponse":" MWENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782735423","data":{"timestamp":" 946782735422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIMJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782738943","data":{"timestamp":" 946782738943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutatambaa tutatembea!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUTATAMBAA"," userResponse":" HATUTATAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782740902","data":{"timestamp":" 946782740901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutatambaa tutatembea!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTATEMBEA"," userResponse":" TUTATEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782743351","data":{"timestamp":" 946782743350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyoka hao walijikunjua polepole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782743904","data":{"timestamp":" 946782743903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyoka hao walijikunjua polepole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782745341","data":{"timestamp":" 946782745340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyoka hao walijikunjua polepole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIJIKUNJUA"," userResponse":" WALIJIKUNJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782746892","data":{"timestamp":" 946782746891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyoka hao walijikunjua polepole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLEPOLE"," userResponse":" POLEPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782749872","data":{"timestamp":" 946782749871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAANZA"," userResponse":" WAKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782751081","data":{"timestamp":" 946782751080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGELEA"," userResponse":" KUOGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782751358","data":{"timestamp":" 946782751358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782752640","data":{"timestamp":" 946782752639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGELEA"," userResponse":" KUOGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782754015","data":{"timestamp":" 946782754015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" WAKIELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782754544","data":{"timestamp":" 946782754543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782755576","data":{"timestamp":" 946782755575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782756495","data":{"timestamp":" 946782756494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGAZA"," userResponse":" MWANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782760285","data":{"timestamp":" 946782760284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokaribia juu ya maji maajabu yalitendeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKARIBIA"," userResponse":" WALIPOKARIBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782760746","data":{"timestamp":" 946782760745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokaribia juu ya maji maajabu yalitendeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782760967","data":{"timestamp":" 946782760967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokaribia juu ya maji maajabu yalitendeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782761744","data":{"timestamp":" 946782761743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokaribia juu ya maji maajabu yalitendeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782763118","data":{"timestamp":" 946782763118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokaribia juu ya maji maajabu yalitendeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAAJABU"," userResponse":" MAAJABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782764302","data":{"timestamp":" 946782764302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokaribia juu ya maji maajabu yalitendeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALITENDEKA"," userResponse":" YALITENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782766832","data":{"timestamp":" 946782766831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKIA"," userResponse":" MIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782767175","data":{"timestamp":" 946782767175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782768692","data":{"timestamp":" 946782768691"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIGAWIKA"," userResponse":" ILIGAWIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782769506","data":{"timestamp":" 946782769505"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782770106","data":{"timestamp":" 946782770106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782771147","data":{"timestamp":" 946782771146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAWA"," userResponse":" WAKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782771412","data":{"timestamp":" 946782771412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782772074","data":{"timestamp":" 946782772074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782772557","data":{"timestamp":" 946782772553"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782773163","data":{"timestamp":" 946782773163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782775370","data":{"timestamp":" 946782775369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782776080","data":{"timestamp":" 946782776079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" MIKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782776850","data":{"timestamp":" 946782776849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWILI"," userResponse":" MIWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782777155","data":{"timestamp":" 946782777154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782777914","data":{"timestamp":" 946782777914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782779075","data":{"timestamp":" 946782779074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOKEA"," userResponse":" ILITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782779697","data":{"timestamp":" 946782779697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782779771","data":{"timestamp":" 946782779771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782780296","data":{"timestamp":" 946782780296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWA"," userResponse":" VICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782780886","data":{"timestamp":" 946782780885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAO"," userResponse":" VYAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782784116","data":{"timestamp":" 946782784116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782784623","data":{"timestamp":" 946782784623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782785227","data":{"timestamp":" 946782785227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782785979","data":{"timestamp":" 946782785978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782786691","data":{"timestamp":" 946782786691"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782787928","data":{"timestamp":" 946782787927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIGEUKA"," userResponse":" WALIGEUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782788134","data":{"timestamp":" 946782788134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782788583","data":{"timestamp":" 946782788582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782789092","data":{"timestamp":" 946782789091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUME"," userResponse":" MUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782789310","data":{"timestamp":" 946782789310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782789874","data":{"timestamp":" 946782789874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782793192","data":{"timestamp":" 946782793191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAZAMANA"," userResponse":" WALITAZAMANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782793869","data":{"timestamp":" 946782793868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782794957","data":{"timestamp":" 946782794956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENDANA"," userResponse":" KUPENDANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782795476","data":{"timestamp":" 946782795475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782795954","data":{"timestamp":" 946782795952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUME"," userResponse":" MUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782796203","data":{"timestamp":" 946782796202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782796701","data":{"timestamp":" 946782796701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782800047","data":{"timestamp":" 946782800046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAJENGA"," userResponse":" TUTAJENGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782800613","data":{"timestamp":" 946782800612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782801141","data":{"timestamp":" 946782801141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782802198","data":{"timestamp":" 946782802197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782802962","data":{"timestamp":" 946782802961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782803732","data":{"timestamp":" 946782803731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782806234","data":{"timestamp":" 946782806233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782806825","data":{"timestamp":" 946782806824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782808012","data":{"timestamp":" 946782808012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTALIONA"," userResponse":" TUTALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782808469","data":{"timestamp":" 946782808469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782809540","data":{"timestamp":" 946782809539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKITOKA"," userResponse":" LIKITOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782810117","data":{"timestamp":" 946782810116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782811156","data":{"timestamp":" 946782811156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" KUFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782811676","data":{"timestamp":" 946782811674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782812205","data":{"timestamp":" 946782812205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782814349","data":{"timestamp":" 946782814349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782815397","data":{"timestamp":" 946782815396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTALINDA"," userResponse":" TUTALINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782815996","data":{"timestamp":" 946782815995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782816233","data":{"timestamp":" 946782816232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782816864","data":{"timestamp":" 946782816863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782817629","data":{"timestamp":" 946782817627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUME"," userResponse":" MUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782818496","data":{"timestamp":" 946782818495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782821239","data":{"timestamp":" 946782821237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKUWA"," userResponse":" TUTAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782822198","data":{"timestamp":" 946782822198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782822410","data":{"timestamp":" 946782822409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782822934","data":{"timestamp":" 946782822933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782823193","data":{"timestamp":" 946782823192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782823931","data":{"timestamp":" 946782823930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782827413","data":{"timestamp":" 946782827412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782828023","data":{"timestamp":" 946782828021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782828845","data":{"timestamp":" 946782828845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUME"," userResponse":" MUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782829072","data":{"timestamp":" 946782829071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782829682","data":{"timestamp":" 946782829681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782830652","data":{"timestamp":" 946782830652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782833253","data":{"timestamp":" 946782833252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAAM"," userResponse":" NAAM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782834402","data":{"timestamp":" 946782834402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" AKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782834679","data":{"timestamp":" 946782834678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782834875","data":{"timestamp":" 946782834874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782835514","data":{"timestamp":" 946782835513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782837843","data":{"timestamp":" 946782837843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782838924","data":{"timestamp":" 946782838923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATEMBEA"," userResponse":" WAKATEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782839772","data":{"timestamp":" 946782839771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782840279","data":{"timestamp":" 946782840278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782841320","data":{"timestamp":" 946782841319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMWENGU"," userResponse":" ULIMWENGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782841787","data":{"timestamp":" 946782841786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782842376","data":{"timestamp":" 946782842375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_41__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782845015","data":{"timestamp":" 946782845013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782845162","data":{"timestamp":" 946782845162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 967000a1-d7ad-428d-b53c-391083850052"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_41__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782863712","data":{"timestamp":" 946782863712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" c80fac8a-3793-4917-9186-e7c30dd6a3e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782910487","data":{"timestamp":" 946782910486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" c80fac8a-3793-4917-9186-e7c30dd6a3e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782910602","data":{"timestamp":" 946782910602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" c80fac8a-3793-4917-9186-e7c30dd6a3e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782934998","data":{"timestamp":" 946782934997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782935189","data":{"timestamp":" 946782935189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782936010","data":{"timestamp":" 946782936009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782936672","data":{"timestamp":" 946782936671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782937465","data":{"timestamp":" 946782937464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782938032","data":{"timestamp":" 946782938031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782938995","data":{"timestamp":" 946782938994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782939735","data":{"timestamp":" 946782939735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWALI"," userResponse":" AWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782940887","data":{"timestamp":" 946782940886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGAWAJE"," userResponse":" INGAWAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782941478","data":{"timestamp":" 946782941478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABIA"," userResponse":" TABIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782942082","data":{"timestamp":" 946782942081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782943196","data":{"timestamp":" 946782943196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782944063","data":{"timestamp":" 946782944063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782944988","data":{"timestamp":" 946782944987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782945735","data":{"timestamp":" 946782945735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782946191","data":{"timestamp":" 946782946190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782946965","data":{"timestamp":" 946782946964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782949420","data":{"timestamp":" 946782949420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782950153","data":{"timestamp":" 946782950152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782950901","data":{"timestamp":" 946782950900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782951885","data":{"timestamp":" 946782951884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782952353","data":{"timestamp":" 946782952352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782953274","data":{"timestamp":" 946782953274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782954444","data":{"timestamp":" 946782954443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782955272","data":{"timestamp":" 946782955272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782955620","data":{"timestamp":" 946782955619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782958589","data":{"timestamp":" 946782958588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782959229","data":{"timestamp":" 946782959228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782960052","data":{"timestamp":" 946782960052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782960656","data":{"timestamp":" 946782960654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782960855","data":{"timestamp":" 946782960854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782961484","data":{"timestamp":" 946782961483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782963114","data":{"timestamp":" 946782963113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFAHAMU"," userResponse":" KUMFAHAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782964095","data":{"timestamp":" 946782964094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782964663","data":{"timestamp":" 946782964663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782965102","data":{"timestamp":" 946782965101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782967863","data":{"timestamp":" 946782967862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782968511","data":{"timestamp":" 946782968510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782969590","data":{"timestamp":" 946782969589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782970044","data":{"timestamp":" 946782970043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782970835","data":{"timestamp":" 946782970835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEUPE"," userResponse":" CHEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782971706","data":{"timestamp":" 946782971705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOPO"," userResponse":" KILICHOPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782972097","data":{"timestamp":" 946782972096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782972201","data":{"timestamp":" 946782972201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782972578","data":{"timestamp":" 946782972578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" SHINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782973262","data":{"timestamp":" 946782973261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKO"," userResponse":" LAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782973765","data":{"timestamp":" 946782973765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782974133","data":{"timestamp":" 946782974133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782975016","data":{"timestamp":" 946782975015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782976872","data":{"timestamp":" 946782976872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782977460","data":{"timestamp":" 946782977459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782978388","data":{"timestamp":" 946782978387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782979254","data":{"timestamp":" 946782979254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782980016","data":{"timestamp":" 946782980016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782980929","data":{"timestamp":" 946782980928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INALIWA"," userResponse":" INALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782981979","data":{"timestamp":" 946782981979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782982922","data":{"timestamp":" 946782982922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPORUKA"," userResponse":" NINAPORUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782983623","data":{"timestamp":" 946782983622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782986341","data":{"timestamp":" 946782986340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEKUWA"," userResponse":" NIMEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782987399","data":{"timestamp":" 946782987398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAILA"," userResponse":" NINAILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782988408","data":{"timestamp":" 946782988408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782988775","data":{"timestamp":" 946782988775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782989505","data":{"timestamp":" 946782989505"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782990546","data":{"timestamp":" 946782990545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782991121","data":{"timestamp":" 946782991120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782992598","data":{"timestamp":" 946782992597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMENIBANDIKA"," userResponse":" IMENIBANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782993477","data":{"timestamp":" 946782993477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGONI"," userResponse":" SHINGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782997225","data":{"timestamp":" 946782997224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782997706","data":{"timestamp":" 946782997705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782997837","data":{"timestamp":" 946782997836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782998504","data":{"timestamp":" 946782998503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946782999544","data":{"timestamp":" 946782999543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783000516","data":{"timestamp":" 946783000515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKWA"," userResponse":" ALITOKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783000756","data":{"timestamp":" 946783000755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783001429","data":{"timestamp":" 946783001428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDENDA"," userResponse":" UDENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783002332","data":{"timestamp":" 946783002331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783002900","data":{"timestamp":" 946783002899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783003440","data":{"timestamp":" 946783003440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783003550","data":{"timestamp":" 946783003550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783003920","data":{"timestamp":" 946783003919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783004399","data":{"timestamp":" 946783004399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783006677","data":{"timestamp":" 946783006676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783007623","data":{"timestamp":" 946783007622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783008366","data":{"timestamp":" 946783008365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783009104","data":{"timestamp":" 946783009103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783009641","data":{"timestamp":" 946783009640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783010167","data":{"timestamp":" 946783010166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783012988","data":{"timestamp":" 946783012987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783014678","data":{"timestamp":" 946783014678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAIPATAJE"," userResponse":" ATAIPATAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783015400","data":{"timestamp":" 946783015400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783015840","data":{"timestamp":" 946783015839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783016722","data":{"timestamp":" 946783016722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783017250","data":{"timestamp":" 946783017249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALI"," userResponse":" HALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783017805","data":{"timestamp":" 946783017804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783018331","data":{"timestamp":" 946783018330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783018531","data":{"timestamp":" 946783018530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783019623","data":{"timestamp":" 946783019622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIRUKIA"," userResponse":" KUIRUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783022272","data":{"timestamp":" 946783022272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783022980","data":{"timestamp":" 946783022979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783023671","data":{"timestamp":" 946783023671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783024610","data":{"timestamp":" 946783024610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783025496","data":{"timestamp":" 946783025495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOPESHA"," userResponse":" KUKOPESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783026295","data":{"timestamp":" 946783026294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783027031","data":{"timestamp":" 946783027030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783027630","data":{"timestamp":" 946783027630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIWEZE"," userResponse":" NIWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783028994","data":{"timestamp":" 946783028994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," userResponse":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783029748","data":{"timestamp":" 946783029748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783032208","data":{"timestamp":" 946783032207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783032697","data":{"timestamp":" 946783032696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783033650","data":{"timestamp":" 946783033649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783034553","data":{"timestamp":" 946783034552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783035134","data":{"timestamp":" 946783035133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783035676","data":{"timestamp":" 946783035676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783038495","data":{"timestamp":" 946783038495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783039224","data":{"timestamp":" 946783039223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783042398","data":{"timestamp":" 946783042397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783042598","data":{"timestamp":" 946783042598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783043377","data":{"timestamp":" 946783043377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKARIMU"," userResponse":" UKARIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783043814","data":{"timestamp":" 946783043813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783044895","data":{"timestamp":" 946783044895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783045386","data":{"timestamp":" 946783045386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783046108","data":{"timestamp":" 946783046107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783048387","data":{"timestamp":" 946783048386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783049616","data":{"timestamp":" 946783049616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYASHONA"," userResponse":" ALIYASHONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783050112","data":{"timestamp":" 946783050112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAWE"," userResponse":" YAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783050733","data":{"timestamp":" 946783050732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783054061","data":{"timestamp":" 946783054060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAYAUNGANISHA"," userResponse":" AKAYAUNGANISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783054337","data":{"timestamp":" 946783054336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783054845","data":{"timestamp":" 946783054845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783055398","data":{"timestamp":" 946783055398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783056701","data":{"timestamp":" 946783056701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJARIBU"," userResponse":" AKAJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783057396","data":{"timestamp":" 946783057395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783060321","data":{"timestamp":" 946783060320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783060860","data":{"timestamp":" 946783060860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZITO"," userResponse":" UZITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783061248","data":{"timestamp":" 946783061247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783062179","data":{"timestamp":" 946783062179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMSHINDA"," userResponse":" ULIMSHINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783064896","data":{"timestamp":" 946783064896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783065816","data":{"timestamp":" 946783065815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIBIDI"," userResponse":" ILIBIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783066689","data":{"timestamp":" 946783066688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFIKIRIE"," userResponse":" AFIKIRIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783067278","data":{"timestamp":" 946783067277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPANGO"," userResponse":" MPANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783067897","data":{"timestamp":" 946783067896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783071732","data":{"timestamp":" 946783071731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783072448","data":{"timestamp":" 946783072447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783072864","data":{"timestamp":" 946783072864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783073920","data":{"timestamp":" 946783073920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783075004","data":{"timestamp":" 946783075003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKUSHIKE"," userResponse":" NIKUSHIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783075161","data":{"timestamp":" 946783075160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783075793","data":{"timestamp":" 946783075792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783076431","data":{"timestamp":" 946783076431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783077843","data":{"timestamp":" 946783077842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAKAPORUKA"," userResponse":" UTAKAPORUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783078796","data":{"timestamp":" 946783078796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783081605","data":{"timestamp":" 946783081605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783082331","data":{"timestamp":" 946783082330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783084807","data":{"timestamp":" 946783084807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783085363","data":{"timestamp":" 946783085363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783086524","data":{"timestamp":" 946783086524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKUBALI"," userResponse":" AKAKUBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783087164","data":{"timestamp":" 946783087163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783090147","data":{"timestamp":" 946783090147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783090533","data":{"timestamp":" 946783090533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783091021","data":{"timestamp":" 946783091020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783091703","data":{"timestamp":" 946783091703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783094371","data":{"timestamp":" 946783094371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783094999","data":{"timestamp":" 946783094998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUFANYE"," userResponse":" TUFANYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783095444","data":{"timestamp":" 946783095443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783096316","data":{"timestamp":" 946783096316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783099796","data":{"timestamp":" 946783099795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUCHA"," userResponse":" ILIPOKUCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783100243","data":{"timestamp":" 946783100242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783100923","data":{"timestamp":" 946783100922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783101950","data":{"timestamp":" 946783101948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783102866","data":{"timestamp":" 946783102866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSHIKA"," userResponse":" ALIMSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783103264","data":{"timestamp":" 946783103263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783103868","data":{"timestamp":" 946783103868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783104376","data":{"timestamp":" 946783104376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783104909","data":{"timestamp":" 946783104908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783105726","data":{"timestamp":" 946783105726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783106408","data":{"timestamp":" 946783106407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783107162","data":{"timestamp":" 946783107162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" AKARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783107986","data":{"timestamp":" 946783107985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783110805","data":{"timestamp":" 946783110804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783111604","data":{"timestamp":" 946783111603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783112715","data":{"timestamp":" 946783112714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITAMANI"," userResponse":" AKITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783113318","data":{"timestamp":" 946783113317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783114202","data":{"timestamp":" 946783114202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783115132","data":{"timestamp":" 946783115131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783116045","data":{"timestamp":" 946783116044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783116796","data":{"timestamp":" 946783116794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783117707","data":{"timestamp":" 946783117706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOKWA"," userResponse":" AKATOKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783117872","data":{"timestamp":" 946783117871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783118575","data":{"timestamp":" 946783118574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDENDA"," userResponse":" UDENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783119072","data":{"timestamp":" 946783119072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783121538","data":{"timestamp":" 946783121538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783122808","data":{"timestamp":" 946783122807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" ALIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783123442","data":{"timestamp":" 946783123441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783124475","data":{"timestamp":" 946783124473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783125546","data":{"timestamp":" 946783125546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAKA"," userResponse":" MPAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783126716","data":{"timestamp":" 946783126716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKACHOKA"," userResponse":" AKACHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783127373","data":{"timestamp":" 946783127373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783130043","data":{"timestamp":" 946783130043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783130561","data":{"timestamp":" 946783130560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783131553","data":{"timestamp":" 946783131553"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWOMBA"," userResponse":" AKAMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783132963","data":{"timestamp":" 946783132963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDELEA"," userResponse":" ENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783133725","data":{"timestamp":" 946783133724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783134064","data":{"timestamp":" 946783134063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783134837","data":{"timestamp":" 946783134836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783135218","data":{"timestamp":" 946783135218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783138939","data":{"timestamp":" 946783138938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783139759","data":{"timestamp":" 946783139758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPANDE"," userResponse":" KIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783140074","data":{"timestamp":" 946783140074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783140752","data":{"timestamp":" 946783140751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783141287","data":{"timestamp":" 946783141287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783141762","data":{"timestamp":" 946783141761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783142441","data":{"timestamp":" 946783142441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783143326","data":{"timestamp":" 946783143325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783144327","data":{"timestamp":" 946783144326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIKIA"," userResponse":" ALISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783145550","data":{"timestamp":" 946783145549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSHTUKO"," userResponse":" MSHTUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783148202","data":{"timestamp":" 946783148201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNYOYA"," userResponse":" UNYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783148971","data":{"timestamp":" 946783148970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783150307","data":{"timestamp":" 946783150306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOUSHIKA"," userResponse":" ALIOUSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783151487","data":{"timestamp":" 946783151486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKATOKA"," userResponse":" UKATOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783152154","data":{"timestamp":" 946783152153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783152398","data":{"timestamp":" 946783152398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783153126","data":{"timestamp":" 946783153126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783155392","data":{"timestamp":" 946783155392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783156296","data":{"timestamp":" 946783156295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSHTUKO"," userResponse":" MSHTUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783156959","data":{"timestamp":" 946783156959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783157663","data":{"timestamp":" 946783157663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783157852","data":{"timestamp":" 946783157851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783158388","data":{"timestamp":" 946783158388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783160937","data":{"timestamp":" 946783160936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783162320","data":{"timestamp":" 946783162320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJISIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIJISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783163435","data":{"timestamp":" 946783163434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEONDOLEWA"," userResponse":" AMEONDOLEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783164146","data":{"timestamp":" 946783164145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783164928","data":{"timestamp":" 946783164927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZIGO"," userResponse":" MZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783165158","data":{"timestamp":" 946783165157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783165793","data":{"timestamp":" 946783165792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783166292","data":{"timestamp":" 946783166291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783167164","data":{"timestamp":" 946783167164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAPONA"," userResponse":" UKAPONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783169845","data":{"timestamp":" 946783169845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIIMBA"," userResponse":" ALIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783171618","data":{"timestamp":" 946783171616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783171681","data":{"timestamp":" 946783171681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783172775","data":{"timestamp":" 946783172774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783174227","data":{"timestamp":" 946783174226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINYONYOE"," userResponse":" JINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783176749","data":{"timestamp":" 946783176748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783177208","data":{"timestamp":" 946783177208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783178265","data":{"timestamp":" 946783178265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783179463","data":{"timestamp":" 946783179462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINYONYOE"," userResponse":" JINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783182465","data":{"timestamp":" 946783182464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783183713","data":{"timestamp":" 946783183713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUITIKIA"," userResponse":" KUITIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783184578","data":{"timestamp":" 946783184577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783185428","data":{"timestamp":" 946783185428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIIMBA"," userResponse":" ALIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783186363","data":{"timestamp":" 946783186362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYUME"," userResponse":" KINYUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783187947","data":{"timestamp":" 946783187946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783188083","data":{"timestamp":" 946783188083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783189067","data":{"timestamp":" 946783189066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783190179","data":{"timestamp":" 946783190179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIKANE"," userResponse":" SHIKANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783192421","data":{"timestamp":" 946783192421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIJINYONYOE"," userResponse":" YASIJINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783195341","data":{"timestamp":" 946783195341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783195467","data":{"timestamp":" 946783195467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783196425","data":{"timestamp":" 946783196424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783197617","data":{"timestamp":" 946783197616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIKANE"," userResponse":" SHIKANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783199488","data":{"timestamp":" 946783199487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIJINYONYOE"," userResponse":" YASIJINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783203432","data":{"timestamp":" 946783203431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATIMAYE"," userResponse":" HATIMAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783204280","data":{"timestamp":" 946783204279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783206058","data":{"timestamp":" 946783206057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAMWACHILIA"," userResponse":" YAKAMWACHILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783206677","data":{"timestamp":" 946783206677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatimaye manyoya yakamwachilia fisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783209550","data":{"timestamp":" 946783209549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa peke yake angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783210120","data":{"timestamp":" 946783210119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa peke yake angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783210578","data":{"timestamp":" 946783210578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa peke yake angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783211602","data":{"timestamp":" 946783211602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa peke yake angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783214666","data":{"timestamp":" 946783214665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKIA"," userResponse":" ALIRUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783215210","data":{"timestamp":" 946783215209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783215989","data":{"timestamp":" 946783215989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783217480","data":{"timestamp":" 946783217479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" AKIFIKIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783218537","data":{"timestamp":" 946783218536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOKULA"," userResponse":" ANAPOKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783219002","data":{"timestamp":" 946783219001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783219668","data":{"timestamp":" 946783219667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783220787","data":{"timestamp":" 946783220786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ITAMPA"," userResponse":" ITAMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783221930","data":{"timestamp":" 946783221929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSINGI"," userResponse":" MSINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783222119","data":{"timestamp":" 946783222118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783222931","data":{"timestamp":" 946783222930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirukia nyama nono akifikiri anapokula nyama nono itampa msingi wa kukalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKALIA"," userResponse":" KUKALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783225427","data":{"timestamp":" 946783225426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783226456","data":{"timestamp":" 946783226455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOJARIBU"," userResponse":" ALIPOJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783227104","data":{"timestamp":" 946783227104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHIKA"," userResponse":" KUSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783227776","data":{"timestamp":" 946783227775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783229401","data":{"timestamp":" 946783229401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOSHIKA"," userResponse":" ALICHOSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783230414","data":{"timestamp":" 946783230413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783231268","data":{"timestamp":" 946783231267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGU"," userResponse":" MAWINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783232024","data":{"timestamp":" 946783232024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783232906","data":{"timestamp":" 946783232905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIMAJI"," userResponse":" MAJIMAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783233233","data":{"timestamp":" 946783233233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipojaribu kushika nyama alichoshika kilikuwa mawingu ya majimaji tu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783236232","data":{"timestamp":" 946783236231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783237409","data":{"timestamp":" 946783237408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHAANZA"," userResponse":" AMESHAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783238338","data":{"timestamp":" 946783238338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGUKA"," userResponse":" KUANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783239439","data":{"timestamp":" 946783239438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" UPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783240297","data":{"timestamp":" 946783240296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ameshaanza kuanguka upesi upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" UPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783243936","data":{"timestamp":" 946783243936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie nisaidie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" NISAIDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783245384","data":{"timestamp":" 946783245383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie nisaidie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" NISAIDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783248292","data":{"timestamp":" 946783248292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783249097","data":{"timestamp":" 946783249096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783249632","data":{"timestamp":" 946783249632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783250069","data":{"timestamp":" 946783250068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYOTE"," userResponse":" YEYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783250538","data":{"timestamp":" 946783250538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783251716","data":{"timestamp":" 946783251716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSIKILIZA"," userResponse":" KUMSIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783254373","data":{"timestamp":" 946783254372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783255082","data":{"timestamp":" 946783255082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWISHA"," userResponse":" ALIKWISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783255800","data":{"timestamp":" 946783255800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POTEA"," userResponse":" POTEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783256689","data":{"timestamp":" 946783256688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alikwisha potea mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGUNI"," userResponse":" MAWINGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783259754","data":{"timestamp":" 946783259753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783260770","data":{"timestamp":" 946783260769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANGUKA"," userResponse":" AKAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783261012","data":{"timestamp":" 946783261011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783261951","data":{"timestamp":" 946783261950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHINDO"," userResponse":" KISHINDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783263230","data":{"timestamp":" 946783263229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783264208","data":{"timestamp":" 946783264207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783264662","data":{"timestamp":" 946783264661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi akaanguka kwa kishindo akalala kimya muda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783267672","data":{"timestamp":" 946783267671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMKA"," userResponse":" AKAAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783268739","data":{"timestamp":" 946783268739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPIGA"," userResponse":" AKIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783269224","data":{"timestamp":" 946783269224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOWE"," userResponse":" YOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783270064","data":{"timestamp":" 946783270063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783271013","data":{"timestamp":" 946783271012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUMIVU"," userResponse":" MAUMIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783271636","data":{"timestamp":" 946783271635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783272918","data":{"timestamp":" 946783272917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEVUNJIKA"," userResponse":" UMEVUNJIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783273657","data":{"timestamp":" 946783273657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOVU"," userResponse":" KOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783274439","data":{"timestamp":" 946783274438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783275462","data":{"timestamp":" 946783275462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akaamka akipiga yowe ya maumivu mguu umevunjika kovu nyingi mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILINI"," userResponse":" MWILINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783279258","data":{"timestamp":" 946783279257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hajaweza kuruka kamwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAJAWEZA"," userResponse":" HAJAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783280499","data":{"timestamp":" 946783280499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hajaweza kuruka kamwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783281427","data":{"timestamp":" 946783281427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hajaweza kuruka kamwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMWE"," userResponse":" KAMWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783283790","data":{"timestamp":" 946783283789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783284759","data":{"timestamp":" 946783284758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" URAFIKI"," userResponse":" URAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783285302","data":{"timestamp":" 946783285302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAINA"," userResponse":" BAINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783285799","data":{"timestamp":" 946783285798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783285984","data":{"timestamp":" 946783285984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783286628","data":{"timestamp":" 946783286627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783288328","data":{"timestamp":" 946783288327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEPO"," userResponse":" HAKUWEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783288775","data":{"timestamp":" 946783288775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783291436","data":{"timestamp":" 946783291433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783291566","data":{"timestamp":" 946783291566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8790571f-568d-4c16-8df8-6edc11a943a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na urafiki baina yake na kunguru hakuwepo tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783318367","data":{"timestamp":" 946783318366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783320435","data":{"timestamp":" 946783320435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783322043","data":{"timestamp":" 946783322042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783325929","data":{"timestamp":" 946783325928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783327542","data":{"timestamp":" 946783327541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783329679","data":{"timestamp":" 946783329678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783331274","data":{"timestamp":" 946783331273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783333225","data":{"timestamp":" 946783333225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783334821","data":{"timestamp":" 946783334820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783337039","data":{"timestamp":" 946783337038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783338639","data":{"timestamp":" 946783338639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783340823","data":{"timestamp":" 946783340822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783342414","data":{"timestamp":" 946783342413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783344584","data":{"timestamp":" 946783344583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783346190","data":{"timestamp":" 946783346189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783365539","data":{"timestamp":" 946783365538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783367162","data":{"timestamp":" 946783367161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783371453","data":{"timestamp":" 946783371453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783373042","data":{"timestamp":" 946783373041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783375364","data":{"timestamp":" 946783375363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783376990","data":{"timestamp":" 946783376989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783384539","data":{"timestamp":" 946783384539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783386155","data":{"timestamp":" 946783386155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783390098","data":{"timestamp":" 946783390098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783391707","data":{"timestamp":" 946783391706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783394952","data":{"timestamp":" 946783394951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783396584","data":{"timestamp":" 946783396583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783400284","data":{"timestamp":" 946783400284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783401888","data":{"timestamp":" 946783401887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783404498","data":{"timestamp":" 946783404497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783406103","data":{"timestamp":" 946783406102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783408488","data":{"timestamp":" 946783408488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783410085","data":{"timestamp":" 946783410084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783412381","data":{"timestamp":" 946783412380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783413980","data":{"timestamp":" 946783413979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783416223","data":{"timestamp":" 946783416222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783417828","data":{"timestamp":" 946783417827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783420072","data":{"timestamp":" 946783420072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783421681","data":{"timestamp":" 946783421681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783423892","data":{"timestamp":" 946783423891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783425496","data":{"timestamp":" 946783425495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783427753","data":{"timestamp":" 946783427753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783429357","data":{"timestamp":" 946783429356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783431837","data":{"timestamp":" 946783431837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783433457","data":{"timestamp":" 946783433457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783442231","data":{"timestamp":" 946783442230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" START_Y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783443277","data":{"timestamp":" 946783443277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783444868","data":{"timestamp":" 946783444868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783448076","data":{"timestamp":" 946783448075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783450105","data":{"timestamp":" 946783450103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783450204","data":{"timestamp":" 946783450204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" b0c95a53-d1f8-45a9-8c21-126a1db3296d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783473654","data":{"timestamp":" 946783473653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783474392","data":{"timestamp":" 946783474391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783474635","data":{"timestamp":" 946783474634"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783475343","data":{"timestamp":" 946783475343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783476337","data":{"timestamp":" 946783476336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783477133","data":{"timestamp":" 946783477132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783477434","data":{"timestamp":" 946783477434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783478462","data":{"timestamp":" 946783478461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783481295","data":{"timestamp":" 946783481295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" WALITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783482295","data":{"timestamp":" 946783482294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783483084","data":{"timestamp":" 946783483083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783483600","data":{"timestamp":" 946783483599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783484531","data":{"timestamp":" 946783484529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BINADAMU"," userResponse":" BINADAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783485176","data":{"timestamp":" 946783485175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783485877","data":{"timestamp":" 946783485876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783486708","data":{"timestamp":" 946783486708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIVYO"," userResponse":" WALIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783489103","data":{"timestamp":" 946783489102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783489519","data":{"timestamp":" 946783489518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783490300","data":{"timestamp":" 946783490300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUPI"," userResponse":" YUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783491490","data":{"timestamp":" 946783491489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESTAHILI"," userResponse":" ANGESTAHILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783491927","data":{"timestamp":" 946783491926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783492987","data":{"timestamp":" 946783492986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783496235","data":{"timestamp":" 946783496234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783497080","data":{"timestamp":" 946783497079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783498234","data":{"timestamp":" 946783498234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NKWAZI"," userResponse":" NKWAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783500858","data":{"timestamp":" 946783500858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783501195","data":{"timestamp":" 946783501195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783501915","data":{"timestamp":" 946783501914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783503075","data":{"timestamp":" 946783503074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783503302","data":{"timestamp":" 946783503302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783503521","data":{"timestamp":" 946783503520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783504412","data":{"timestamp":" 946783504411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFALME"," userResponse":" KIFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783506736","data":{"timestamp":" 946783506735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783507635","data":{"timestamp":" 946783507635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783510627","data":{"timestamp":" 946783510627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783511639","data":{"timestamp":" 946783511638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783512421","data":{"timestamp":" 946783512420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJI"," userResponse":" TAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783513012","data":{"timestamp":" 946783513012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783514447","data":{"timestamp":" 946783514447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOITANA"," userResponse":" ANAPOITANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783515466","data":{"timestamp":" 946783515466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783515855","data":{"timestamp":" 946783515854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783516124","data":{"timestamp":" 946783516123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783516263","data":{"timestamp":" 946783516263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783517678","data":{"timestamp":" 946783517677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783518882","data":{"timestamp":" 946783518882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783520047","data":{"timestamp":" 946783520046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783520991","data":{"timestamp":" 946783520990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783523162","data":{"timestamp":" 946783523162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783523996","data":{"timestamp":" 946783523995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783524489","data":{"timestamp":" 946783524487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783525199","data":{"timestamp":" 946783525199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783525951","data":{"timestamp":" 946783525950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783527014","data":{"timestamp":" 946783527013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" NDIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783528157","data":{"timestamp":" 946783528156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783529022","data":{"timestamp":" 946783529021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783529165","data":{"timestamp":" 946783529165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783529982","data":{"timestamp":" 946783529981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783530585","data":{"timestamp":" 946783530584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783531238","data":{"timestamp":" 946783531238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783532945","data":{"timestamp":" 946783532945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNGURUMA"," userResponse":" HUNGURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783533601","data":{"timestamp":" 946783533600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783534374","data":{"timestamp":" 946783534374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783535628","data":{"timestamp":" 946783535628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783536932","data":{"timestamp":" 946783536932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEZEA"," userResponse":" ALIWAELEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783539289","data":{"timestamp":" 946783539288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783540545","data":{"timestamp":" 946783540544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWEZI"," userResponse":" HAWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783541414","data":{"timestamp":" 946783541413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783544326","data":{"timestamp":" 946783544325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783544520","data":{"timestamp":" 946783544520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783545053","data":{"timestamp":" 946783545053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783545743","data":{"timestamp":" 946783545743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783546457","data":{"timestamp":" 946783546456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWEZE"," userResponse":" AWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783547275","data":{"timestamp":" 946783547274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783551488","data":{"timestamp":" 946783551487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" NAFIKIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783552186","data":{"timestamp":" 946783552186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAWEZA"," userResponse":" NINAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783552614","data":{"timestamp":" 946783552614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783553625","data":{"timestamp":" 946783553624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783554638","data":{"timestamp":" 946783554637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783555522","data":{"timestamp":" 946783555521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783556425","data":{"timestamp":" 946783556424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783557365","data":{"timestamp":" 946783557364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUNGA"," userResponse":" AKIPUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783557947","data":{"timestamp":" 946783557946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783558498","data":{"timestamp":" 946783558498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783561353","data":{"timestamp":" 946783561353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783561669","data":{"timestamp":" 946783561668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783562916","data":{"timestamp":" 946783562916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783564516","data":{"timestamp":" 946783564516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783567801","data":{"timestamp":" 946783567801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNARINGA"," userResponse":" UNARINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783568519","data":{"timestamp":" 946783568519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783569603","data":{"timestamp":" 946783569602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783570271","data":{"timestamp":" 946783570270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KHOVA"," userResponse":" KHOVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783571461","data":{"timestamp":" 946783571461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" BUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783572456","data":{"timestamp":" 946783572455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783575162","data":{"timestamp":" 946783575161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISITOSHE"," userResponse":" ISITOSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783576152","data":{"timestamp":" 946783576152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783576691","data":{"timestamp":" 946783576689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783577040","data":{"timestamp":" 946783577039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783578261","data":{"timestamp":" 946783578260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAFRIKA"," userResponse":" MWAFRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783581128","data":{"timestamp":" 946783581127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783581936","data":{"timestamp":" 946783581935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783582947","data":{"timestamp":" 946783582946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783583718","data":{"timestamp":" 946783583718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783584400","data":{"timestamp":" 946783584399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHINDA"," userResponse":" KUSHINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783584612","data":{"timestamp":" 946783584611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783585246","data":{"timestamp":" 946783585245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783585807","data":{"timestamp":" 946783585807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783589416","data":{"timestamp":" 946783589415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASTAHILI"," userResponse":" NINASTAHILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783589942","data":{"timestamp":" 946783589942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783590673","data":{"timestamp":" 946783590671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783593235","data":{"timestamp":" 946783593234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783594116","data":{"timestamp":" 946783594115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783594603","data":{"timestamp":" 946783594602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783595297","data":{"timestamp":" 946783595296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" BUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783596332","data":{"timestamp":" 946783596332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" WALIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783597051","data":{"timestamp":" 946783597050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783600090","data":{"timestamp":" 946783600090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783600699","data":{"timestamp":" 946783600698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUENDA"," userResponse":" HUENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783601598","data":{"timestamp":" 946783601597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783602428","data":{"timestamp":" 946783602427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783603848","data":{"timestamp":" 946783603847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAPOCHOMOZA"," userResponse":" LINAPOCHOMOZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783606860","data":{"timestamp":" 946783606860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo hawakuafikiana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783607740","data":{"timestamp":" 946783607739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo hawakuafikiana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783609708","data":{"timestamp":" 946783609707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo hawakuafikiana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUAFIKIANA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUAFIKIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783612152","data":{"timestamp":" 946783612151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783612770","data":{"timestamp":" 946783612769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783613737","data":{"timestamp":" 946783613737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPIGA"," userResponse":" ALIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783614232","data":{"timestamp":" 946783614232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783615653","data":{"timestamp":" 946783615653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783616965","data":{"timestamp":" 946783616964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKAYERUKA"," userResponse":" ATAKAYERUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783617966","data":{"timestamp":" 946783617965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783618697","data":{"timestamp":" 946783618697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783619741","data":{"timestamp":" 946783619741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKUWA"," userResponse":" ATAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783620376","data":{"timestamp":" 946783620375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783623189","data":{"timestamp":" 946783623188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783624176","data":{"timestamp":" 946783624175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783625317","data":{"timestamp":" 946783625317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" WALIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783625825","data":{"timestamp":" 946783625825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783626625","data":{"timestamp":" 946783626625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783627084","data":{"timestamp":" 946783627083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783628125","data":{"timestamp":" 946783628124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKARUKA"," userResponse":" WAKARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783628654","data":{"timestamp":" 946783628654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783630011","data":{"timestamp":" 946783630010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783630721","data":{"timestamp":" 946783630721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783633547","data":{"timestamp":" 946783633546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783634267","data":{"timestamp":" 946783634266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUKINI"," userResponse":" BUKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783635190","data":{"timestamp":" 946783635189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" ALIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783635468","data":{"timestamp":" 946783635468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783636032","data":{"timestamp":" 946783636028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783636754","data":{"timestamp":" 946783636753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" NZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783637989","data":{"timestamp":" 946783637988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783638233","data":{"timestamp":" 946783638233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783638704","data":{"timestamp":" 946783638704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783639371","data":{"timestamp":" 946783639370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783639472","data":{"timestamp":" 946783639472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783640274","data":{"timestamp":" 946783640274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" MILIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783641235","data":{"timestamp":" 946783641235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIREFU"," userResponse":" MIREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783642147","data":{"timestamp":" 946783642146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783643044","data":{"timestamp":" 946783643043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIANI"," userResponse":" DUNIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783645600","data":{"timestamp":" 946783645600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783646592","data":{"timestamp":" 946783646591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783648133","data":{"timestamp":" 946783648132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NKWAZI"," userResponse":" NKWAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783649794","data":{"timestamp":" 946783649794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" ALIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783650022","data":{"timestamp":" 946783650021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783650603","data":{"timestamp":" 946783650603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783651484","data":{"timestamp":" 946783651483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783652456","data":{"timestamp":" 946783652456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783653139","data":{"timestamp":" 946783653138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783653253","data":{"timestamp":" 946783653253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783653703","data":{"timestamp":" 946783653702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783654652","data":{"timestamp":" 946783654652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783655385","data":{"timestamp":" 946783655385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783655628","data":{"timestamp":" 946783655628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783656184","data":{"timestamp":" 946783656184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" MILIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783658677","data":{"timestamp":" 946783658676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783659370","data":{"timestamp":" 946783659369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783659958","data":{"timestamp":" 946783659957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783660735","data":{"timestamp":" 946783660735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGO"," userResponse":" MGONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783661496","data":{"timestamp":" 946783661495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEUPE"," userResponse":" MWEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783663206","data":{"timestamp":" 946783663205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" ALIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783664162","data":{"timestamp":" 946783664162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783665073","data":{"timestamp":" 946783665073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783665393","data":{"timestamp":" 946783665392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783666055","data":{"timestamp":" 946783666055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783667048","data":{"timestamp":" 946783667048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783668126","data":{"timestamp":" 946783668125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783669119","data":{"timestamp":" 946783669118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSIMAMA"," userResponse":" KUSIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783670274","data":{"timestamp":" 946783670273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783670516","data":{"timestamp":" 946783670515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783671079","data":{"timestamp":" 946783671079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783672383","data":{"timestamp":" 946783672382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUELEKEA"," userResponse":" KUELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783672866","data":{"timestamp":" 946783672865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783673349","data":{"timestamp":" 946783673349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783675884","data":{"timestamp":" 946783675883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783676509","data":{"timestamp":" 946783676508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783677117","data":{"timestamp":" 946783677116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783678346","data":{"timestamp":" 946783678345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMSIKIA"," userResponse":" WALIMSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783678892","data":{"timestamp":" 946783678891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783680099","data":{"timestamp":" 946783680099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPAZA"," userResponse":" AKIPAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783680881","data":{"timestamp":" 946783680880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783681627","data":{"timestamp":" 946783681626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKISEMA"," userResponse":" AKISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783682939","data":{"timestamp":" 946783682939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIMI"," userResponse":" NDIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783683253","data":{"timestamp":" 946783683252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783683970","data":{"timestamp":" 946783683969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783685374","data":{"timestamp":" 946783685372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783686351","data":{"timestamp":" 946783686350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783686987","data":{"timestamp":" 946783686987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" NDIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783688351","data":{"timestamp":" 946783688351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783691621","data":{"timestamp":" 946783691620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783692590","data":{"timestamp":" 946783692589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIKIA"," userResponse":" ALISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783693419","data":{"timestamp":" 946783693418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783693875","data":{"timestamp":" 946783693874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783694328","data":{"timestamp":" 946783694327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783695456","data":{"timestamp":" 946783695455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TINK"," userResponse":" TINK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783696189","data":{"timestamp":" 946783696188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TINK"," userResponse":" TINK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783696999","data":{"timestamp":" 946783696998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TINK"," userResponse":" TINK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783699338","data":{"timestamp":" 946783699337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783699558","data":{"timestamp":" 946783699558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783700086","data":{"timestamp":" 946783700085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783700846","data":{"timestamp":" 946783700845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783701995","data":{"timestamp":" 946783701994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783702292","data":{"timestamp":" 946783702291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783702971","data":{"timestamp":" 946783702971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783703201","data":{"timestamp":" 946783703200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783703843","data":{"timestamp":" 946783703842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783704383","data":{"timestamp":" 946783704382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783704957","data":{"timestamp":" 946783704956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783705458","data":{"timestamp":" 946783705457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783706139","data":{"timestamp":" 946783706138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783707569","data":{"timestamp":" 946783707569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCEDE"," userResponse":" NCEDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783708608","data":{"timestamp":" 946783708608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NEDDICKY"," userResponse":" NEDDICKY"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783711541","data":{"timestamp":" 946783711541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783713021","data":{"timestamp":" 946783713020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHIKILIA"," userResponse":" AMESHIKILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783713671","data":{"timestamp":" 946783713671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783714501","data":{"timestamp":" 946783714499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNYOYA"," userResponse":" UNYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783715210","data":{"timestamp":" 946783715210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783715980","data":{"timestamp":" 946783715980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783716218","data":{"timestamp":" 946783716217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783716867","data":{"timestamp":" 946783716866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783720249","data":{"timestamp":" 946783720248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUTANISHINDA"," userResponse":" HUTANISHINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783720909","data":{"timestamp":" 946783720908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783722059","data":{"timestamp":" 946783722058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783722954","data":{"timestamp":" 946783722953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783723417","data":{"timestamp":" 946783723416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783723911","data":{"timestamp":" 946783723910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783724801","data":{"timestamp":" 946783724801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPAA"," userResponse":" AKAPAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783725744","data":{"timestamp":" 946783725744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783726474","data":{"timestamp":" 946783726474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783727268","data":{"timestamp":" 946783727267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783730508","data":{"timestamp":" 946783730507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliruka juu zaidi ya ndege yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" ALIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783730905","data":{"timestamp":" 946783730904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliruka juu zaidi ya ndege yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783731713","data":{"timestamp":" 946783731713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliruka juu zaidi ya ndege yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783731830","data":{"timestamp":" 946783731830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliruka juu zaidi ya ndege yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783732259","data":{"timestamp":" 946783732258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliruka juu zaidi ya ndege yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783733192","data":{"timestamp":" 946783733191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliruka juu zaidi ya ndege yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYOTE"," userResponse":" YEYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783735697","data":{"timestamp":" 946783735696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko juu zaidi ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKO"," userResponse":" NIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783736411","data":{"timestamp":" 946783736410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko juu zaidi ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783737127","data":{"timestamp":" 946783737127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko juu zaidi ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783737229","data":{"timestamp":" 946783737229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko juu zaidi ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783737775","data":{"timestamp":" 946783737774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko juu zaidi ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783738548","data":{"timestamp":" 946783738547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko juu zaidi ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783741327","data":{"timestamp":" 946783741327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ndiye mfalme wenu alisema kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783741989","data":{"timestamp":" 946783741988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ndiye mfalme wenu alisema kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" NDIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783742835","data":{"timestamp":" 946783742834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ndiye mfalme wenu alisema kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783743452","data":{"timestamp":" 946783743451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ndiye mfalme wenu alisema kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENU"," userResponse":" WENU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783744773","data":{"timestamp":" 946783744773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ndiye mfalme wenu alisema kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783745063","data":{"timestamp":" 946783745063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ndiye mfalme wenu alisema kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783745879","data":{"timestamp":" 946783745878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ndiye mfalme wenu alisema kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783749298","data":{"timestamp":" 946783749297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783750006","data":{"timestamp":" 946783750005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783750673","data":{"timestamp":" 946783750673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783750862","data":{"timestamp":" 946783750861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783751810","data":{"timestamp":" 946783751809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAWA"," userResponse":" UBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783753571","data":{"timestamp":" 946783753570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALITOKEZEA"," userResponse":" PALITOKEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783754129","data":{"timestamp":" 946783754128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783754682","data":{"timestamp":" 946783754681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783755383","data":{"timestamp":" 946783755382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783757746","data":{"timestamp":" 946783757745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TINK"," userResponse":" TINK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783758563","data":{"timestamp":" 946783758562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TINK"," userResponse":" TINK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783761095","data":{"timestamp":" 946783761094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TINK"," userResponse":" TINK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783761913","data":{"timestamp":" 946783761912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TINK"," userResponse":" TINK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783764102","data":{"timestamp":" 946783764101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783764720","data":{"timestamp":" 946783764720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783765480","data":{"timestamp":" 946783765479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783766625","data":{"timestamp":" 946783766624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783769450","data":{"timestamp":" 946783769447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIMI"," userResponse":" NDIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783770447","data":{"timestamp":" 946783770447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" MFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783771425","data":{"timestamp":" 946783771424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENU"," userResponse":" WENU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783774052","data":{"timestamp":" 946783774052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783774874","data":{"timestamp":" 946783774873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783776235","data":{"timestamp":" 946783776234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMECHOKA"," userResponse":" AMECHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783777997","data":{"timestamp":" 946783777997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANGEWEZA"," userResponse":" HANGEWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783778753","data":{"timestamp":" 946783778752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783779553","data":{"timestamp":" 946783779552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783779742","data":{"timestamp":" 946783779740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783780345","data":{"timestamp":" 946783780344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783782920","data":{"timestamp":" 946783782920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783783627","data":{"timestamp":" 946783783627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783784687","data":{"timestamp":" 946783784686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUKA"," userResponse":" ALISHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783785428","data":{"timestamp":" 946783785427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783786438","data":{"timestamp":" 946783786437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783787609","data":{"timestamp":" 946783787608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEAMBATANA"," userResponse":" AMEAMBATANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783788220","data":{"timestamp":" 946783788220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783788950","data":{"timestamp":" 946783788949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCEDE"," userResponse":" NCEDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783790000","data":{"timestamp":" 946783789999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAWANI"," userResponse":" UBAWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783792310","data":{"timestamp":" 946783792310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783793291","data":{"timestamp":" 946783793290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783794458","data":{"timestamp":" 946783794457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783795837","data":{"timestamp":" 946783795836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAMEANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783796528","data":{"timestamp":" 946783796527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783797068","data":{"timestamp":" 946783797068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783797739","data":{"timestamp":" 946783797739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783798496","data":{"timestamp":" 946783798495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783798737","data":{"timestamp":" 946783798736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783799627","data":{"timestamp":" 946783799627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783802672","data":{"timestamp":" 946783802672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimsubiri tayari kuyang'oa manyoya yake yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMSUBIRI"," userResponse":" WALIMSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783804355","data":{"timestamp":" 946783804354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimsubiri tayari kuyang'oa manyoya yake yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783805463","data":{"timestamp":" 946783805462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimsubiri tayari kuyang'oa manyoya yake yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYANG"," userResponse":" KUYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783805474","data":{"timestamp":" 946783805474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimsubiri tayari kuyang'oa manyoya yake yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" OA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783806626","data":{"timestamp":" 946783806626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimsubiri tayari kuyang'oa manyoya yake yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783807387","data":{"timestamp":" 946783807387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimsubiri tayari kuyang'oa manyoya yake yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783808122","data":{"timestamp":" 946783808122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimsubiri tayari kuyang'oa manyoya yake yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783811691","data":{"timestamp":" 946783811690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783812123","data":{"timestamp":" 946783812122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783812719","data":{"timestamp":" 946783812718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783813656","data":{"timestamp":" 946783813655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783814893","data":{"timestamp":" 946783814892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783816119","data":{"timestamp":" 946783816118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEPESI"," userResponse":" MWEPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783816343","data":{"timestamp":" 946783816342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783816975","data":{"timestamp":" 946783816974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJUA"," userResponse":" KUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783817626","data":{"timestamp":" 946783817625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783818776","data":{"timestamp":" 946783818775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783819049","data":{"timestamp":" 946783819049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783819871","data":{"timestamp":" 946783819870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783821921","data":{"timestamp":" 946783821920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783822658","data":{"timestamp":" 946783822657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783823965","data":{"timestamp":" 946783823964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBILIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783825136","data":{"timestamp":" 946783825136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783825944","data":{"timestamp":" 946783825943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783826436","data":{"timestamp":" 946783826435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIMO"," userResponse":" SHIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783826577","data":{"timestamp":" 946783826576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783827148","data":{"timestamp":" 946783827148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783829724","data":{"timestamp":" 946783829723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783830302","data":{"timestamp":" 946783830301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783830580","data":{"timestamp":" 946783830579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783831225","data":{"timestamp":" 946783831224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783832193","data":{"timestamp":" 946783832193"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783833433","data":{"timestamp":" 946783833432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783834383","data":{"timestamp":" 946783834382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULINDE"," userResponse":" ULINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783834893","data":{"timestamp":" 946783834892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIMO"," userResponse":" SHIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783835737","data":{"timestamp":" 946783835736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783836670","data":{"timestamp":" 946783836669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783837975","data":{"timestamp":" 946783837975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMKAMATE"," userResponse":" UMKAMATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783839160","data":{"timestamp":" 946783839159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOTOKA"," userResponse":" ANAPOTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783839702","data":{"timestamp":" 946783839702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783841401","data":{"timestamp":" 946783841400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" WALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783842003","data":{"timestamp":" 946783842002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" BUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783844033","data":{"timestamp":" 946783844032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bundi aliketi mbele ya shimo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783844592","data":{"timestamp":" 946783844591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bundi aliketi mbele ya shimo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783845219","data":{"timestamp":" 946783845218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bundi aliketi mbele ya shimo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" BUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783846246","data":{"timestamp":" 946783846245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bundi aliketi mbele ya shimo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKETI"," userResponse":" ALIKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783846694","data":{"timestamp":" 946783846694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bundi aliketi mbele ya shimo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783846951","data":{"timestamp":" 946783846951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bundi aliketi mbele ya shimo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783847633","data":{"timestamp":" 946783847633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bundi aliketi mbele ya shimo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIMO"," userResponse":" SHIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783850903","data":{"timestamp":" 946783850902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783851320","data":{"timestamp":" 946783851319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783852098","data":{"timestamp":" 946783852098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783852268","data":{"timestamp":" 946783852268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783852887","data":{"timestamp":" 946783852887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783853135","data":{"timestamp":" 946783853134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783853886","data":{"timestamp":" 946783853885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783854819","data":{"timestamp":" 946783854818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783855539","data":{"timestamp":" 946783855538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783855976","data":{"timestamp":" 946783855976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783857120","data":{"timestamp":" 946783857120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783858242","data":{"timestamp":" 946783858241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" BUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783860107","data":{"timestamp":" 946783860106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" ALILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783862382","data":{"timestamp":" 946783862381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783862964","data":{"timestamp":" 946783862964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783863634","data":{"timestamp":" 946783863633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783865177","data":{"timestamp":" 946783865176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUNGULIA"," userResponse":" ALICHUNGULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783865756","data":{"timestamp":" 946783865756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783866494","data":{"timestamp":" 946783866493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783868262","data":{"timestamp":" 946783868261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783868282","data":{"timestamp":" 946783868282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIP"," userResponse":" ZIP"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783869852","data":{"timestamp":" 946783869851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOROKEA"," userResponse":" ALITOROKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783871035","data":{"timestamp":" 946783871034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783874079","data":{"timestamp":" 946783874079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" BUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783875670","data":{"timestamp":" 946783875669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAIBIKA"," userResponse":" ALIAIBIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783876178","data":{"timestamp":" 946783876178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783877010","data":{"timestamp":" 946783877009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783877926","data":{"timestamp":" 946783877926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOMZUIA"," userResponse":" KUTOMZUIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783878314","data":{"timestamp":" 946783878314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783878773","data":{"timestamp":" 946783878773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783879761","data":{"timestamp":" 946783879761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOROKA"," userResponse":" KUTOROKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783882202","data":{"timestamp":" 946783882202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa yeye huwinda usiku peke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783882678","data":{"timestamp":" 946783882677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa yeye huwinda usiku peke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783883708","data":{"timestamp":" 946783883707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa yeye huwinda usiku peke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWINDA"," userResponse":" HUWINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783884646","data":{"timestamp":" 946783884646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa yeye huwinda usiku peke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783885326","data":{"timestamp":" 946783885326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa yeye huwinda usiku peke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783888238","data":{"timestamp":" 946783888238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783888475","data":{"timestamp":" 946783888474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783889504","data":{"timestamp":" 946783889503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANA"," userResponse":" MCHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783890766","data":{"timestamp":" 946783890765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULALA"," userResponse":" HULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783892046","data":{"timestamp":" 946783892045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783892613","data":{"timestamp":" 946783892613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783893203","data":{"timestamp":" 946783893202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783893443","data":{"timestamp":" 946783893441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783894053","data":{"timestamp":" 946783894053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783894826","data":{"timestamp":" 946783894825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_43__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783897469","data":{"timestamp":" 946783897467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783897593","data":{"timestamp":" 946783897592"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 28760371-1af1-4bb9-b968-985688fbb6fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_43__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783918591","data":{"timestamp":" 946783918590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783919750","data":{"timestamp":" 946783919749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZALIWA"," userResponse":" ALIZALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783920787","data":{"timestamp":" 946783920786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" MOZAMBIQUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783923272","data":{"timestamp":" 946783923271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHI"," userResponse":" NCHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783923708","data":{"timestamp":" 946783923707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783924498","data":{"timestamp":" 946783924497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783925246","data":{"timestamp":" 946783925245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASKINI"," userResponse":" MASKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783926041","data":{"timestamp":" 946783926040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783926734","data":{"timestamp":" 946783926733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783927670","data":{"timestamp":" 946783927669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783928543","data":{"timestamp":" 946783928542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEPATA"," userResponse":" WAMEPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783929219","data":{"timestamp":" 946783929218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UHURU"," userResponse":" UHURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783931908","data":{"timestamp":" 946783931907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783932959","data":{"timestamp":" 946783932958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783933196","data":{"timestamp":" 946783933195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783933765","data":{"timestamp":" 946783933765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783934380","data":{"timestamp":" 946783934379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783934610","data":{"timestamp":" 946783934609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783935298","data":{"timestamp":" 946783935297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783937810","data":{"timestamp":" 946783937809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783938615","data":{"timestamp":" 946783938613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783938851","data":{"timestamp":" 946783938850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783939462","data":{"timestamp":" 946783939461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783939666","data":{"timestamp":" 946783939665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783940396","data":{"timestamp":" 946783940395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPA"," userResponse":" KUWAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783941059","data":{"timestamp":" 946783941058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" WANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783942294","data":{"timestamp":" 946783942294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783943389","data":{"timestamp":" 946783943389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783944233","data":{"timestamp":" 946783944233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783944607","data":{"timestamp":" 946783944607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783945612","data":{"timestamp":" 946783945611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783947427","data":{"timestamp":" 946783947427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAINGEWEZEKANA"," userResponse":" HAINGEWEZEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783950482","data":{"timestamp":" 946783950482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783951085","data":{"timestamp":" 946783951085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783952008","data":{"timestamp":" 946783952008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKUWA"," userResponse":" ANGEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783952962","data":{"timestamp":" 946783952962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZALIWA"," userResponse":" MZALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783953136","data":{"timestamp":" 946783953136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783953699","data":{"timestamp":" 946783953699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783956085","data":{"timestamp":" 946783956084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LICHA"," userResponse":" LICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783956299","data":{"timestamp":" 946783956298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783956983","data":{"timestamp":" 946783956983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783957646","data":{"timestamp":" 946783957646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783958170","data":{"timestamp":" 946783958170"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783959305","data":{"timestamp":" 946783959305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783959589","data":{"timestamp":" 946783959589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783960443","data":{"timestamp":" 946783960443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783961198","data":{"timestamp":" 946783961197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783961882","data":{"timestamp":" 946783961882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783962529","data":{"timestamp":" 946783962529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783963585","data":{"timestamp":" 946783963585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783964580","data":{"timestamp":" 946783964580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKUFA"," userResponse":" ANAKUFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783967324","data":{"timestamp":" 946783967323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOTA"," userResponse":" ALIOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783967817","data":{"timestamp":" 946783967817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783968451","data":{"timestamp":" 946783968451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783968894","data":{"timestamp":" 946783968894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783969757","data":{"timestamp":" 946783969757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783970402","data":{"timestamp":" 946783970402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEENDA"," userResponse":" ANGEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783970837","data":{"timestamp":" 946783970836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783971841","data":{"timestamp":" 946783971841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783974438","data":{"timestamp":" 946783974438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783975173","data":{"timestamp":" 946783975173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783975697","data":{"timestamp":" 946783975696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783977041","data":{"timestamp":" 946783977041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGEMSAIDIA"," userResponse":" INGEMSAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783977875","data":{"timestamp":" 946783977874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783980635","data":{"timestamp":" 946783980634"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMII"," userResponse":" JAMII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783981129","data":{"timestamp":" 946783981128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783982103","data":{"timestamp":" 946783982102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAPA"," userResponse":" ILIAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783983107","data":{"timestamp":" 946783983107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTIMIZA"," userResponse":" KUTIMIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783983682","data":{"timestamp":" 946783983681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783984266","data":{"timestamp":" 946783984265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jamii yake iliapa kutimiza ndoto yake."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783987149","data":{"timestamp":" 946783987148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIKI"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783987676","data":{"timestamp":" 946783987676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHACHE"," userResponse":" CHACHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783988262","data":{"timestamp":" 946783988262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783988520","data":{"timestamp":" 946783988519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783989036","data":{"timestamp":" 946783989035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFO"," userResponse":" KIFO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783989283","data":{"timestamp":" 946783989283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783990139","data":{"timestamp":" 946783990138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783991187","data":{"timestamp":" 946783991186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783992060","data":{"timestamp":" 946783992060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPEWA"," userResponse":" ALIPEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783992612","data":{"timestamp":" 946783992611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783993578","data":{"timestamp":" 946783993577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUAMBATA"," userResponse":" KUAMBATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783993930","data":{"timestamp":" 946783993930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783994496","data":{"timestamp":" 946783994496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UREMBO"," userResponse":" UREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783995150","data":{"timestamp":" 946783995150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783997650","data":{"timestamp":" 946783997650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" ALIITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946783998339","data":{"timestamp":" 946783998338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784000871","data":{"timestamp":" 946784000870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KADRI"," userResponse":" KADRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784001499","data":{"timestamp":" 946784001498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784002580","data":{"timestamp":" 946784002579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" ILIPOZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784003573","data":{"timestamp":" 946784003572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYOYOMA"," userResponse":" KUYOYOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784004603","data":{"timestamp":" 946784004602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784005223","data":{"timestamp":" 946784005222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784006078","data":{"timestamp":" 946784006078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784006712","data":{"timestamp":" 946784006711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULETA"," userResponse":" KULETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784007640","data":{"timestamp":" 946784007639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784008221","data":{"timestamp":" 946784008221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784010891","data":{"timestamp":" 946784010891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784012059","data":{"timestamp":" 946784012059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAMUA"," userResponse":" ILIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784012858","data":{"timestamp":" 946784012857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPA"," userResponse":" KUMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784013470","data":{"timestamp":" 946784013469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784014281","data":{"timestamp":" 946784014280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784015488","data":{"timestamp":" 946784015487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784018559","data":{"timestamp":" 946784018558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784019548","data":{"timestamp":" 946784019548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITIA"," userResponse":" ALITIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784020076","data":{"timestamp":" 946784020076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDII"," userResponse":" BIDII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784020631","data":{"timestamp":" 946784020629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784021408","data":{"timestamp":" 946784021408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784024018","data":{"timestamp":" 946784024018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784024762","data":{"timestamp":" 946784024762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUZO"," userResponse":" TUZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784025526","data":{"timestamp":" 946784025526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBALO"," userResponse":" AMBALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784026748","data":{"timestamp":" 946784026748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGEBADILISHA"," userResponse":" LINGEBADILISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784027792","data":{"timestamp":" 946784027791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784028400","data":{"timestamp":" 946784028400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784031347","data":{"timestamp":" 946784031346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784032417","data":{"timestamp":" 946784032416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UHISANI"," userResponse":" UHISANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784033359","data":{"timestamp":" 946784033358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUSOMEA"," userResponse":" WAKUSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784033835","data":{"timestamp":" 946784033835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784034824","data":{"timestamp":" 946784034824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784035722","data":{"timestamp":" 946784035721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJNI"," userResponse":" KIJIJNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784038288","data":{"timestamp":" 946784038287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784038816","data":{"timestamp":" 946784038815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784039844","data":{"timestamp":" 946784039843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784040343","data":{"timestamp":" 946784040341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784040830","data":{"timestamp":" 946784040829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784041681","data":{"timestamp":" 946784041680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784044784","data":{"timestamp":" 946784044784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784045509","data":{"timestamp":" 946784045508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784045712","data":{"timestamp":" 946784045712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784046728","data":{"timestamp":" 946784046727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" MOZAMBIQUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784047550","data":{"timestamp":" 946784047549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAJUE"," userResponse":" WAJUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784048293","data":{"timestamp":" 946784048292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784048543","data":{"timestamp":" 946784048542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784049485","data":{"timestamp":" 946784049484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANDIKA"," userResponse":" KUANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784052412","data":{"timestamp":" 946784052411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784053202","data":{"timestamp":" 946784053201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784053872","data":{"timestamp":" 946784053871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAPO"," userResponse":" AMBAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784054651","data":{"timestamp":" 946784054650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784055187","data":{"timestamp":" 946784055187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784056007","data":{"timestamp":" 946784056006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEENDA"," userResponse":" WANGEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784056939","data":{"timestamp":" 946784056939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784059882","data":{"timestamp":" 946784059881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784060780","data":{"timestamp":" 946784060780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITIA"," userResponse":" ALITIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784061599","data":{"timestamp":" 946784061598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDII"," userResponse":" BIDII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784061957","data":{"timestamp":" 946784061957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784062690","data":{"timestamp":" 946784062688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784063950","data":{"timestamp":" 946784063950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784066401","data":{"timestamp":" 946784066400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784067290","data":{"timestamp":" 946784067290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784068421","data":{"timestamp":" 946784068421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784068941","data":{"timestamp":" 946784068941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUZO"," userResponse":" TUZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784069629","data":{"timestamp":" 946784069628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784069744","data":{"timestamp":" 946784069744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784070724","data":{"timestamp":" 946784070723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" KUHUDHURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784071232","data":{"timestamp":" 946784071231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUO"," userResponse":" CHUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784072022","data":{"timestamp":" 946784072022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUU"," userResponse":" KIKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784072887","data":{"timestamp":" 946784072886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKO"," userResponse":" HUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784073717","data":{"timestamp":" 946784073716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PORTUGAL"," userResponse":" PORTUGAL"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784076389","data":{"timestamp":" 946784076389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784077310","data":{"timestamp":" 946784077309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784078291","data":{"timestamp":" 946784078290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784079952","data":{"timestamp":" 946784079952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIFUNZA"," userResponse":" AKAJIFUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784080442","data":{"timestamp":" 946784080441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LUGHA"," userResponse":" LUGHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784081224","data":{"timestamp":" 946784081223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784081987","data":{"timestamp":" 946784081986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GENI"," userResponse":" GENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784082410","data":{"timestamp":" 946784082410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784083354","data":{"timestamp":" 946784083353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASOMA"," userResponse":" AKASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784084348","data":{"timestamp":" 946784084347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITABU"," userResponse":" VITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784084977","data":{"timestamp":" 946784084977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINGI"," userResponse":" VINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784085720","data":{"timestamp":" 946784085719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPYA"," userResponse":" VIPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784088307","data":{"timestamp":" 946784088307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONA"," userResponse":" AKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784088855","data":{"timestamp":" 946784088854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784089469","data":{"timestamp":" 946784089469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784090044","data":{"timestamp":" 946784090043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784090498","data":{"timestamp":" 946784090498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784091281","data":{"timestamp":" 946784091280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784092573","data":{"timestamp":" 946784092572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITIMIA"," userResponse":" IKITIMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784094999","data":{"timestamp":" 946784094998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784095847","data":{"timestamp":" 946784095846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIMPA"," userResponse":" ILIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784096810","data":{"timestamp":" 946784096809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784097733","data":{"timestamp":" 946784097732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784098770","data":{"timestamp":" 946784098769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784099263","data":{"timestamp":" 946784099262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784100033","data":{"timestamp":" 946784100033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784100313","data":{"timestamp":" 946784100313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784101216","data":{"timestamp":" 946784101215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ilimpa furaha kubwa lakini bado alikuwa na huzuni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784103961","data":{"timestamp":" 946784103961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784104517","data":{"timestamp":" 946784104516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784105316","data":{"timestamp":" 946784105315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784106336","data":{"timestamp":" 946784106335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784106852","data":{"timestamp":" 946784106851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784107752","data":{"timestamp":" 946784107751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784107993","data":{"timestamp":" 946784107992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784108627","data":{"timestamp":" 946784108627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UHURU"," userResponse":" UHURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784111423","data":{"timestamp":" 946784111422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784111979","data":{"timestamp":" 946784111978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784112561","data":{"timestamp":" 946784112560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784113367","data":{"timestamp":" 946784113366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784113595","data":{"timestamp":" 946784113594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784114615","data":{"timestamp":" 946784114615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784116147","data":{"timestamp":" 946784116147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UJUZI"," userResponse":" UJUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784116680","data":{"timestamp":" 946784116679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784117783","data":{"timestamp":" 946784117782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUMAINI"," userResponse":" MATUMAINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784120074","data":{"timestamp":" 946784120073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784120983","data":{"timestamp":" 946784120982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784121231","data":{"timestamp":" 946784121230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784122307","data":{"timestamp":" 946784122306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784123049","data":{"timestamp":" 946784123048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAO"," userResponse":" AMBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784124003","data":{"timestamp":" 946784124002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHISI"," userResponse":" WALIHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784124454","data":{"timestamp":" 946784124454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784125227","data":{"timestamp":" 946784125226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784126012","data":{"timestamp":" 946784126012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784126285","data":{"timestamp":" 946784126284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784126939","data":{"timestamp":" 946784126938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKI"," userResponse":" HAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784127018","data":{"timestamp":" 946784127018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784127805","data":{"timestamp":" 946784127805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784128000","data":{"timestamp":" 946784127999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784128833","data":{"timestamp":" 946784128832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784131366","data":{"timestamp":" 946784131365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAKA"," userResponse":" ALITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784132324","data":{"timestamp":" 946784132323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784133015","data":{"timestamp":" 946784133014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UJUZI"," userResponse":" UJUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784133647","data":{"timestamp":" 946784133647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784134371","data":{"timestamp":" 946784134371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784135271","data":{"timestamp":" 946784135270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784135790","data":{"timestamp":" 946784135789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784136501","data":{"timestamp":" 946784136501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULETA"," userResponse":" KULETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784137543","data":{"timestamp":" 946784137543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABADILIKO"," userResponse":" MABADILIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784138097","data":{"timestamp":" 946784138096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784139180","data":{"timestamp":" 946784139179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitaka kutumia ujuzi wake na marafiki wake kuleta mabadiliko kwao Mozambique."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" MOZAMBIQUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784142222","data":{"timestamp":" 946784142221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAIS"," userResponse":" RAIS"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784143762","data":{"timestamp":" 946784143761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYECHAGULIWA"," userResponse":" ALIYECHAGULIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784144955","data":{"timestamp":" 946784144954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIONGOZA"," userResponse":" KUIONGOZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784145704","data":{"timestamp":" 946784145704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHI"," userResponse":" NCHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784145874","data":{"timestamp":" 946784145873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784146887","data":{"timestamp":" 946784146887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" MOZAMBIQUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784147981","data":{"timestamp":" 946784147979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784148664","data":{"timestamp":" 946784148664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784149124","data":{"timestamp":" 946784149123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784150106","data":{"timestamp":" 946784150106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMORA"," userResponse":" SAMORA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784150859","data":{"timestamp":" 946784150859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACGEL"," userResponse":" MACGEL"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784154116","data":{"timestamp":" 946784154116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPENDANA"," userResponse":" WALIPENDANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784154362","data":{"timestamp":" 946784154361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784155250","data":{"timestamp":" 946784155250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipendana na wakaona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAONA"," userResponse":" WAKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784158843","data":{"timestamp":" 946784158842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784159762","data":{"timestamp":" 946784159761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPEWA"," userResponse":" ALIPEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784160437","data":{"timestamp":" 946784160436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784162005","data":{"timestamp":" 946784162004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKUHAKIKISHA"," userResponse":" YAKUHAKIKISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784163017","data":{"timestamp":" 946784163016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784163507","data":{"timestamp":" 946784163507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784164363","data":{"timestamp":" 946784164363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPATA"," userResponse":" WALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784165036","data":{"timestamp":" 946784165036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784166011","data":{"timestamp":" 946784166010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784168755","data":{"timestamp":" 946784168754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784169282","data":{"timestamp":" 946784169281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784169920","data":{"timestamp":" 946784169919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUMU"," userResponse":" NGUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784170466","data":{"timestamp":" 946784170465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784171125","data":{"timestamp":" 946784171124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784171611","data":{"timestamp":" 946784171611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784171790","data":{"timestamp":" 946784171789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784172634","data":{"timestamp":" 946784172633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" MOZAMBIQUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784174171","data":{"timestamp":" 946784174170"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUJUA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784174908","data":{"timestamp":" 946784174907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784175138","data":{"timestamp":" 946784175136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784176042","data":{"timestamp":" 946784176042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANDIKA"," userResponse":" KUANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784178872","data":{"timestamp":" 946784178869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784179149","data":{"timestamp":" 946784179148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784180236","data":{"timestamp":" 946784180235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784180863","data":{"timestamp":" 946784180863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784181562","data":{"timestamp":" 946784181562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784182793","data":{"timestamp":" 946784182792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kwa kuwapeleka watoto wote shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784185913","data":{"timestamp":" 946784185912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784186259","data":{"timestamp":" 946784186258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784187034","data":{"timestamp":" 946784187033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMORA"," userResponse":" SAMORA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784188074","data":{"timestamp":" 946784188074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIJALIWA"," userResponse":" WALIJALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784188746","data":{"timestamp":" 946784188745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784189533","data":{"timestamp":" 946784189533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784192337","data":{"timestamp":" 946784192337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784192632","data":{"timestamp":" 946784192632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784193234","data":{"timestamp":" 946784193233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784193440","data":{"timestamp":" 946784193439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784194180","data":{"timestamp":" 946784194180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPA"," userResponse":" KUWAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784194819","data":{"timestamp":" 946784194818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784195450","data":{"timestamp":" 946784195450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784196125","data":{"timestamp":" 946784196124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784196645","data":{"timestamp":" 946784196645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784197016","data":{"timestamp":" 946784197015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784198071","data":{"timestamp":" 946784198071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" MOZAMBIQUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784198942","data":{"timestamp":" 946784198942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784200155","data":{"timestamp":" 946784200154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784202442","data":{"timestamp":" 946784202441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784202939","data":{"timestamp":" 946784202938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784203642","data":{"timestamp":" 946784203641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMORA"," userResponse":" SAMORA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784204680","data":{"timestamp":" 946784204679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFA"," userResponse":" AKAFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784205329","data":{"timestamp":" 946784205328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784206150","data":{"timestamp":" 946784206150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJALI"," userResponse":" AJALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784206229","data":{"timestamp":" 946784206229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784206849","data":{"timestamp":" 946784206848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Samora akafa kwa ajali ya ndege."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784209903","data":{"timestamp":" 946784209903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784211813","data":{"timestamp":" 946784211813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOMBOLEZA"," userResponse":" ALIOMBOLEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784212415","data":{"timestamp":" 946784212415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFO"," userResponse":" KIFO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784212754","data":{"timestamp":" 946784212753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784213585","data":{"timestamp":" 946784213584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMORA"," userResponse":" SAMORA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784214295","data":{"timestamp":" 946784214294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784215048","data":{"timestamp":" 946784215047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784216267","data":{"timestamp":" 946784216266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" MINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784219082","data":{"timestamp":" 946784219082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784220252","data":{"timestamp":" 946784220252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784221343","data":{"timestamp":" 946784221342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPENDANA"," userResponse":" WALIPENDANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784221521","data":{"timestamp":" 946784221521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784222180","data":{"timestamp":" 946784222179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELSON"," userResponse":" NELSON"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784223089","data":{"timestamp":" 946784223089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANDELA"," userResponse":" MANDELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784223785","data":{"timestamp":" 946784223784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784224971","data":{"timestamp":" 946784224970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAONA"," userResponse":" WAKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784227822","data":{"timestamp":" 946784227822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784228381","data":{"timestamp":" 946784228380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784228618","data":{"timestamp":" 946784228617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784229329","data":{"timestamp":" 946784229328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784230460","data":{"timestamp":" 946784230459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASAIDIA"," userResponse":" KUWASAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784231171","data":{"timestamp":" 946784231170"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784231428","data":{"timestamp":" 946784231427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784232256","data":{"timestamp":" 946784232256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFRIKA"," userResponse":" AFRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784234820","data":{"timestamp":" 946784234819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946784234946","data":{"timestamp":" 946784234946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" de4e0f05-3a62-450e-bc4a-ee0799cad794"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi kwa pamoja kuwasaidia watoto wa Afrika."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFRIKA"," userResponse":" AFRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787719617","data":{"timestamp":" 946787719617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787720234","data":{"timestamp":" 946787720233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787720448","data":{"timestamp":" 946787720447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787721024","data":{"timestamp":" 946787721024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787722073","data":{"timestamp":" 946787722073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787722327","data":{"timestamp":" 946787722327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787723157","data":{"timestamp":" 946787723156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787723595","data":{"timestamp":" 946787723594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787724254","data":{"timestamp":" 946787724253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mkulima na mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787726896","data":{"timestamp":" 946787726896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787727140","data":{"timestamp":" 946787727140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787727814","data":{"timestamp":" 946787727814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787728408","data":{"timestamp":" 946787728408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787729011","data":{"timestamp":" 946787729011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787730254","data":{"timestamp":" 946787730254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa na mtoto mmoja pekee mvulana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787733104","data":{"timestamp":" 946787733103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliitwa Kisirusiru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" ALIITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787734307","data":{"timestamp":" 946787734307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliitwa Kisirusiru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787737729","data":{"timestamp":" 946787737728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787738389","data":{"timestamp":" 946787738388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787739261","data":{"timestamp":" 946787739260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787740203","data":{"timestamp":" 946787740202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787741362","data":{"timestamp":" 946787741362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787742694","data":{"timestamp":" 946787742693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMPELEKA"," userResponse":" AKIMPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787743586","data":{"timestamp":" 946787743586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787744648","data":{"timestamp":" 946787744647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" MALISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787745860","data":{"timestamp":" 946787745860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787747172","data":{"timestamp":" 946787747171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIIRARUA"," userResponse":" ALIIRARUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787747712","data":{"timestamp":" 946787747711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787748315","data":{"timestamp":" 946787748315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati Kisirusiru alipokuwa akimpeleka mbuzi malishoni mbuzi aliirarua shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787751094","data":{"timestamp":" 946787751093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787752148","data":{"timestamp":" 946787752147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTUMA"," userResponse":" ALIMTUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787752912","data":{"timestamp":" 946787752912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKONI"," userResponse":" SOKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787753704","data":{"timestamp":" 946787753703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787754633","data":{"timestamp":" 946787754633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINDANO"," userResponse":" SINDANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787755557","data":{"timestamp":" 946787755556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787756164","data":{"timestamp":" 946787756164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWEZE"," userResponse":" AWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787756933","data":{"timestamp":" 946787756932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHONA"," userResponse":" KUSHONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787757495","data":{"timestamp":" 946787757494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787758069","data":{"timestamp":" 946787758068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alimtuma sokoni kununua sindano ili aweze kushona shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787761110","data":{"timestamp":" 946787761110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787762124","data":{"timestamp":" 946787762123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUNUA"," userResponse":" ALINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787763038","data":{"timestamp":" 946787763038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINDANO"," userResponse":" SINDANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787763553","data":{"timestamp":" 946787763552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787764436","data":{"timestamp":" 946787764435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIWEKA"," userResponse":" KUIWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787765159","data":{"timestamp":" 946787765158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKIA"," userResponse":" KATIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787765803","data":{"timestamp":" 946787765803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787765997","data":{"timestamp":" 946787765997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787766493","data":{"timestamp":" 946787766492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787767097","data":{"timestamp":" 946787767096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru alinunua sindano na kuiweka katikia mfuko wa shati lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787770522","data":{"timestamp":" 946787770522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787771361","data":{"timestamp":" 946787771360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIENDA"," userResponse":" AKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787772308","data":{"timestamp":" 946787772308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787773803","data":{"timestamp":" 946787773802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPATA"," userResponse":" ALIWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787774658","data":{"timestamp":" 946787774658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787775562","data":{"timestamp":" 946787775562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787776236","data":{"timestamp":" 946787776236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787776501","data":{"timestamp":" 946787776501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787776915","data":{"timestamp":" 946787776915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787780001","data":{"timestamp":" 946787780001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIUNGA"," userResponse":" AKAJIUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787780608","data":{"timestamp":" 946787780608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAO"," userResponse":" NAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787783692","data":{"timestamp":" 946787783692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sindano ilianguka kutoka mfukoni na kupotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINDANO"," userResponse":" SINDANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787784814","data":{"timestamp":" 946787784813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sindano ilianguka kutoka mfukoni na kupotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIANGUKA"," userResponse":" ILIANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787785523","data":{"timestamp":" 946787785523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sindano ilianguka kutoka mfukoni na kupotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787786545","data":{"timestamp":" 946787786545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sindano ilianguka kutoka mfukoni na kupotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKONI"," userResponse":" MFUKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787786858","data":{"timestamp":" 946787786858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sindano ilianguka kutoka mfukoni na kupotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787787755","data":{"timestamp":" 946787787755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sindano ilianguka kutoka mfukoni na kupotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOTEA"," userResponse":" KUPOTEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787791020","data":{"timestamp":" 946787791019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipowasili nyumbani alimwambia mamake kilichotokea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOWASILI"," userResponse":" ALIPOWASILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787792049","data":{"timestamp":" 946787792048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipowasili nyumbani alimwambia mamake kilichotokea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787793793","data":{"timestamp":" 946787793792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipowasili nyumbani alimwambia mamake kilichotokea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787794574","data":{"timestamp":" 946787794573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipowasili nyumbani alimwambia mamake kilichotokea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787796027","data":{"timestamp":" 946787796027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipowasili nyumbani alimwambia mamake kilichotokea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOTOKEA"," userResponse":" KILICHOTOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787798513","data":{"timestamp":" 946787798512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787799032","data":{"timestamp":" 946787799031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787800071","data":{"timestamp":" 946787800070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787800900","data":{"timestamp":" 946787800899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UJAO"," userResponse":" UJAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787801638","data":{"timestamp":" 946787801638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IDUNGE"," userResponse":" IDUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787802392","data":{"timestamp":" 946787802391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINDANO"," userResponse":" SINDANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787802812","data":{"timestamp":" 946787802812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787803855","data":{"timestamp":" 946787803854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787804815","data":{"timestamp":" 946787804814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787805749","data":{"timestamp":" 946787805748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wangu wakati ujao idunge sindano kwenye karatasimamake alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787808086","data":{"timestamp":" 946787808086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787808698","data":{"timestamp":" 946787808697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787809898","data":{"timestamp":" 946787809898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAELEWA"," userResponse":" NAELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787811240","data":{"timestamp":" 946787811239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787812108","data":{"timestamp":" 946787812107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787816152","data":{"timestamp":" 946787816151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata mvulana yule alichukuwa chungu kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787817598","data":{"timestamp":" 946787817597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata mvulana yule alichukuwa chungu kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787818666","data":{"timestamp":" 946787818665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata mvulana yule alichukuwa chungu kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787819165","data":{"timestamp":" 946787819164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata mvulana yule alichukuwa chungu kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787820247","data":{"timestamp":" 946787820247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata mvulana yule alichukuwa chungu kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" ALICHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787820950","data":{"timestamp":" 946787820949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata mvulana yule alichukuwa chungu kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787821551","data":{"timestamp":" 946787821551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata mvulana yule alichukuwa chungu kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787822382","data":{"timestamp":" 946787822381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata mvulana yule alichukuwa chungu kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787825406","data":{"timestamp":" 946787825406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" ALIKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787826783","data":{"timestamp":" 946787826782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOAMBIWA"," userResponse":" ALICHOAMBIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787826992","data":{"timestamp":" 946787826991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787827846","data":{"timestamp":" 946787827846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787828879","data":{"timestamp":" 946787828879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787830301","data":{"timestamp":" 946787830300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIFUNGIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIFUNGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787830924","data":{"timestamp":" 946787830923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787832084","data":{"timestamp":" 946787832084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787832218","data":{"timestamp":" 946787832217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787832941","data":{"timestamp":" 946787832941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPANDE"," userResponse":" KIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787833181","data":{"timestamp":" 946787833181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787834374","data":{"timestamp":" 946787834373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787835188","data":{"timestamp":" 946787835187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787836279","data":{"timestamp":" 946787836278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIBEBA"," userResponse":" KUKIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787836888","data":{"timestamp":" 946787836888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787837816","data":{"timestamp":" 946787837816"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikumbuka alichoambiwa na mamake hivyo alikifungia chungu ndani ya kipande cha karatasi ili kukibeba kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787840138","data":{"timestamp":" 946787840137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787841172","data":{"timestamp":" 946787841171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787842160","data":{"timestamp":" 946787842160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787842881","data":{"timestamp":" 946787842881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787843932","data":{"timestamp":" 946787843931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787845032","data":{"timestamp":" 946787845031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIRARUKA"," userResponse":" ILIRARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787845728","data":{"timestamp":" 946787845727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787846310","data":{"timestamp":" 946787846309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787847566","data":{"timestamp":" 946787847565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKAANGUKA"," userResponse":" KIKAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787848361","data":{"timestamp":" 946787848360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787848791","data":{"timestamp":" 946787848791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787849862","data":{"timestamp":" 946787849861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUNJIKA"," userResponse":" KUVUNJIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787850595","data":{"timestamp":" 946787850594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPANDE"," userResponse":" VIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787851418","data":{"timestamp":" 946787851418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPANDE"," userResponse":" VIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787854127","data":{"timestamp":" 946787854126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787855458","data":{"timestamp":" 946787855457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIMWAGIKA"," userResponse":" YALIMWAGIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787856419","data":{"timestamp":" 946787856419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalimwagika chini."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787859467","data":{"timestamp":" 946787859466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787860446","data":{"timestamp":" 946787860446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787861451","data":{"timestamp":" 946787861450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787862755","data":{"timestamp":" 946787862754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWELEZA"," userResponse":" ALIMWELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787863092","data":{"timestamp":" 946787863091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787863889","data":{"timestamp":" 946787863888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRA"," userResponse":" SUBIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787864950","data":{"timestamp":" 946787864949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787865534","data":{"timestamp":" 946787865533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787866612","data":{"timestamp":" 946787866611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787867403","data":{"timestamp":" 946787867403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UJAO"," userResponse":" UJAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787868259","data":{"timestamp":" 946787868258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIWEKE"," userResponse":" KIWEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787868762","data":{"timestamp":" 946787868762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787869868","data":{"timestamp":" 946787869868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWANI"," userResponse":" KICHWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787872369","data":{"timestamp":" 946787872368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787873653","data":{"timestamp":" 946787873653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAKIBEBA"," userResponse":" UTAKIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787874268","data":{"timestamp":" 946787874268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787875053","data":{"timestamp":" 946787875053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWAGA"," userResponse":" KUMWAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787875747","data":{"timestamp":" 946787875747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787878275","data":{"timestamp":" 946787878274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787878881","data":{"timestamp":" 946787878881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787880171","data":{"timestamp":" 946787880171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAELEWA"," userResponse":" NAELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787881491","data":{"timestamp":" 946787881491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787882563","data":{"timestamp":" 946787882562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo mama naelewa Kisirusiru alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787885796","data":{"timestamp":" 946787885795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata babake Kisirusiru alimweleza aende akawapeleke mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787887227","data":{"timestamp":" 946787887226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata babake Kisirusiru alimweleza aende akawapeleke mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787888262","data":{"timestamp":" 946787888261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata babake Kisirusiru alimweleza aende akawapeleke mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787889482","data":{"timestamp":" 946787889482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata babake Kisirusiru alimweleza aende akawapeleke mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787890947","data":{"timestamp":" 946787890946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata babake Kisirusiru alimweleza aende akawapeleke mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWELEZA"," userResponse":" ALIMWELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787892262","data":{"timestamp":" 946787892261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata babake Kisirusiru alimweleza aende akawapeleke mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AENDE"," userResponse":" AENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787893536","data":{"timestamp":" 946787893535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata babake Kisirusiru alimweleza aende akawapeleke mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAWAPELEKE"," userResponse":" AKAWAPELEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787894128","data":{"timestamp":" 946787894128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata babake Kisirusiru alimweleza aende akawapeleke mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787895307","data":{"timestamp":" 946787895307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata babake Kisirusiru alimweleza aende akawapeleke mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" MALISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787898279","data":{"timestamp":" 946787898278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" ALIKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787898752","data":{"timestamp":" 946787898751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILE"," userResponse":" KILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787899522","data":{"timestamp":" 946787899522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787900762","data":{"timestamp":" 946787900762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787901343","data":{"timestamp":" 946787901343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787901883","data":{"timestamp":" 946787901883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787902924","data":{"timestamp":" 946787902924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" ALIMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787903475","data":{"timestamp":" 946787903474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787904323","data":{"timestamp":" 946787904321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWANI"," userResponse":" KICHWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787906919","data":{"timestamp":" 946787906918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787907900","data":{"timestamp":" 946787907899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPIGA"," userResponse":" ALIMPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787908740","data":{"timestamp":" 946787908740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATEKE"," userResponse":" MATEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787908983","data":{"timestamp":" 946787908982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787910184","data":{"timestamp":" 946787910183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMKWARUZA"," userResponse":" KUMKWARUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787910978","data":{"timestamp":" 946787910977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787913334","data":{"timestamp":" 946787913333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787913844","data":{"timestamp":" 946787913843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAMU"," userResponse":" DAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787914904","data":{"timestamp":" 946787914904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITIRIRIKA"," userResponse":" ILITIRIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787916485","data":{"timestamp":" 946787916484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde damu ilitiririka usoni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USONI"," userResponse":" USONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787918972","data":{"timestamp":" 946787918971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikereka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" LINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787920060","data":{"timestamp":" 946787920059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikereka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAACHA"," userResponse":" UTAACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787920903","data":{"timestamp":" 946787920902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikereka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UJINGA"," userResponse":" UJINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787921519","data":{"timestamp":" 946787921518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikereka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787924422","data":{"timestamp":" 946787924421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikereka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787925772","data":{"timestamp":" 946787925772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikereka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKEREKA"," userResponse":" ALIKEREKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787928979","data":{"timestamp":" 946787928978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuzi hufungwa na kuvutwa kwa kamba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787930080","data":{"timestamp":" 946787930079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuzi hufungwa na kuvutwa kwa kamba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUFUNGWA"," userResponse":" HUFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787930589","data":{"timestamp":" 946787930588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuzi hufungwa na kuvutwa kwa kamba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787931559","data":{"timestamp":" 946787931558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuzi hufungwa na kuvutwa kwa kamba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTWA"," userResponse":" KUVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787931929","data":{"timestamp":" 946787931929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuzi hufungwa na kuvutwa kwa kamba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787932838","data":{"timestamp":" 946787932837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuzi hufungwa na kuvutwa kwa kamba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787935789","data":{"timestamp":" 946787935788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usipokuwa na adabu utalazimika kutoka nyumba hii."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" USIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787936019","data":{"timestamp":" 946787936019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usipokuwa na adabu utalazimika kutoka nyumba hii."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787936895","data":{"timestamp":" 946787936894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usipokuwa na adabu utalazimika kutoka nyumba hii."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADABU"," userResponse":" ADABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787938870","data":{"timestamp":" 946787938869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usipokuwa na adabu utalazimika kutoka nyumba hii."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTALAZIMIKA"," userResponse":" UTALAZIMIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787939743","data":{"timestamp":" 946787939742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usipokuwa na adabu utalazimika kutoka nyumba hii."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787940148","data":{"timestamp":" 946787940148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usipokuwa na adabu utalazimika kutoka nyumba hii."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787940606","data":{"timestamp":" 946787940605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usipokuwa na adabu utalazimika kutoka nyumba hii."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787943477","data":{"timestamp":" 946787943477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata baba alimtuma mwanawe kwenda kununua nyama sokoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787944900","data":{"timestamp":" 946787944900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata baba alimtuma mwanawe kwenda kununua nyama sokoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787945795","data":{"timestamp":" 946787945795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata baba alimtuma mwanawe kwenda kununua nyama sokoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787946779","data":{"timestamp":" 946787946778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata baba alimtuma mwanawe kwenda kununua nyama sokoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTUMA"," userResponse":" ALIMTUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787947574","data":{"timestamp":" 946787947574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata baba alimtuma mwanawe kwenda kununua nyama sokoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787948139","data":{"timestamp":" 946787948139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata baba alimtuma mwanawe kwenda kununua nyama sokoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787949027","data":{"timestamp":" 946787949026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata baba alimtuma mwanawe kwenda kununua nyama sokoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787949600","data":{"timestamp":" 946787949599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata baba alimtuma mwanawe kwenda kununua nyama sokoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787950470","data":{"timestamp":" 946787950469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata baba alimtuma mwanawe kwenda kununua nyama sokoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKONI"," userResponse":" SOKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787953540","data":{"timestamp":" 946787953540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru aliifunga nyama kamba na kuanza kuivuta kuelekea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" AKIKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787954298","data":{"timestamp":" 946787954298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru aliifunga nyama kamba na kuanza kuivuta kuelekea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787955477","data":{"timestamp":" 946787955476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru aliifunga nyama kamba na kuanza kuivuta kuelekea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOAMBIWA"," userResponse":" ALIVYOAMBIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787955717","data":{"timestamp":" 946787955717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru aliifunga nyama kamba na kuanza kuivuta kuelekea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787956616","data":{"timestamp":" 946787956616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru aliifunga nyama kamba na kuanza kuivuta kuelekea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787959679","data":{"timestamp":" 946787959678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru aliifunga nyama kamba na kuanza kuivuta kuelekea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787960942","data":{"timestamp":" 946787960942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru aliifunga nyama kamba na kuanza kuivuta kuelekea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIIFUNGA"," userResponse":" ALIIFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787961491","data":{"timestamp":" 946787961490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru aliifunga nyama kamba na kuanza kuivuta kuelekea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787962142","data":{"timestamp":" 946787962142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru aliifunga nyama kamba na kuanza kuivuta kuelekea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787962712","data":{"timestamp":" 946787962711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru aliifunga nyama kamba na kuanza kuivuta kuelekea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787963408","data":{"timestamp":" 946787963406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru aliifunga nyama kamba na kuanza kuivuta kuelekea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787964519","data":{"timestamp":" 946787964518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru aliifunga nyama kamba na kuanza kuivuta kuelekea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIVUTA"," userResponse":" KUIVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787965781","data":{"timestamp":" 946787965780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru aliifunga nyama kamba na kuanza kuivuta kuelekea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUELEKEA"," userResponse":" KUELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787966755","data":{"timestamp":" 946787966755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru aliifunga nyama kamba na kuanza kuivuta kuelekea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787969971","data":{"timestamp":" 946787969970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia kwa haraka sana ili babake asisubiri kwa muda mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787970301","data":{"timestamp":" 946787970301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia kwa haraka sana ili babake asisubiri kwa muda mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787971135","data":{"timestamp":" 946787971134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia kwa haraka sana ili babake asisubiri kwa muda mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787971648","data":{"timestamp":" 946787971647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia kwa haraka sana ili babake asisubiri kwa muda mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787972406","data":{"timestamp":" 946787972405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia kwa haraka sana ili babake asisubiri kwa muda mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787973126","data":{"timestamp":" 946787973125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia kwa haraka sana ili babake asisubiri kwa muda mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787974303","data":{"timestamp":" 946787974302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia kwa haraka sana ili babake asisubiri kwa muda mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASISUBIRI"," userResponse":" ASISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787974573","data":{"timestamp":" 946787974573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia kwa haraka sana ili babake asisubiri kwa muda mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787975043","data":{"timestamp":" 946787975043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia kwa haraka sana ili babake asisubiri kwa muda mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787975734","data":{"timestamp":" 946787975734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia kwa haraka sana ili babake asisubiri kwa muda mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787977894","data":{"timestamp":" 946787977893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu fikiria jinsi ile nyama ilivyofanana alipowasili nyumbani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787978785","data":{"timestamp":" 946787978784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu fikiria jinsi ile nyama ilivyofanana alipowasili nyumbani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FIKIRIA"," userResponse":" FIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787979364","data":{"timestamp":" 946787979364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu fikiria jinsi ile nyama ilivyofanana alipowasili nyumbani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" JINSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787979701","data":{"timestamp":" 946787979700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu fikiria jinsi ile nyama ilivyofanana alipowasili nyumbani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787980259","data":{"timestamp":" 946787980258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu fikiria jinsi ile nyama ilivyofanana alipowasili nyumbani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787981488","data":{"timestamp":" 946787981488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu fikiria jinsi ile nyama ilivyofanana alipowasili nyumbani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIVYOFANANA"," userResponse":" ILIVYOFANANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787983015","data":{"timestamp":" 946787983014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu fikiria jinsi ile nyama ilivyofanana alipowasili nyumbani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOWASILI"," userResponse":" ALIPOWASILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787983805","data":{"timestamp":" 946787983804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu fikiria jinsi ile nyama ilivyofanana alipowasili nyumbani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787987018","data":{"timestamp":" 946787987017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikasirika mno akamwambia apange vitu vyake na kuondoka pale nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787988555","data":{"timestamp":" 946787988555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikasirika mno akamwambia apange vitu vyake na kuondoka pale nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787989085","data":{"timestamp":" 946787989085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikasirika mno akamwambia apange vitu vyake na kuondoka pale nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787990505","data":{"timestamp":" 946787990504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikasirika mno akamwambia apange vitu vyake na kuondoka pale nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" AKAMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787991212","data":{"timestamp":" 946787991211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikasirika mno akamwambia apange vitu vyake na kuondoka pale nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" APANGE"," userResponse":" APANGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787991556","data":{"timestamp":" 946787991556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikasirika mno akamwambia apange vitu vyake na kuondoka pale nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITU"," userResponse":" VITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787992121","data":{"timestamp":" 946787992120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikasirika mno akamwambia apange vitu vyake na kuondoka pale nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKE"," userResponse":" VYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787992527","data":{"timestamp":" 946787992526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikasirika mno akamwambia apange vitu vyake na kuondoka pale nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787993631","data":{"timestamp":" 946787993630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikasirika mno akamwambia apange vitu vyake na kuondoka pale nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" KUONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787993842","data":{"timestamp":" 946787993842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikasirika mno akamwambia apange vitu vyake na kuondoka pale nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787994646","data":{"timestamp":" 946787994645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake alikasirika mno akamwambia apange vitu vyake na kuondoka pale nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787997139","data":{"timestamp":" 946787997138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake aliposikia hivyo aliamua kuondoka na mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787998120","data":{"timestamp":" 946787998119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake aliposikia hivyo aliamua kuondoka na mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946787998879","data":{"timestamp":" 946787998878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake aliposikia hivyo aliamua kuondoka na mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788000004","data":{"timestamp":" 946788000004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake aliposikia hivyo aliamua kuondoka na mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMUA"," userResponse":" ALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788001275","data":{"timestamp":" 946788001274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake aliposikia hivyo aliamua kuondoka na mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" KUONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788001479","data":{"timestamp":" 946788001478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake aliposikia hivyo aliamua kuondoka na mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788001997","data":{"timestamp":" 946788001997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake aliposikia hivyo aliamua kuondoka na mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788002485","data":{"timestamp":" 946788002484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake aliposikia hivyo aliamua kuondoka na mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788006059","data":{"timestamp":" 946788006059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" WALIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788007529","data":{"timestamp":" 946788007529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" WALICHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788008320","data":{"timestamp":" 946788008319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788008488","data":{"timestamp":" 946788008487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788009330","data":{"timestamp":" 946788009330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788010154","data":{"timestamp":" 946788010153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788010864","data":{"timestamp":" 946788010863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWE"," userResponse":" WAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788011173","data":{"timestamp":" 946788011173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788011776","data":{"timestamp":" 946788011775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788012039","data":{"timestamp":" 946788012038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788012936","data":{"timestamp":" 946788012936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZIA"," userResponse":" KUANZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788014101","data":{"timestamp":" 946788014100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UJENZI"," userResponse":" UJENZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788014323","data":{"timestamp":" 946788014323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788014805","data":{"timestamp":" 946788014805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788015276","data":{"timestamp":" 946788015276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788015950","data":{"timestamp":" 946788015950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoondoka walichukuwa mlango wa jikoni ili wawe na kitu cha kuanzia ujenzi wa nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788019445","data":{"timestamp":" 946788019444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitembea kwa muda mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WALITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788019780","data":{"timestamp":" 946788019779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitembea kwa muda mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788020480","data":{"timestamp":" 946788020479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitembea kwa muda mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788021868","data":{"timestamp":" 946788021868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitembea kwa muda mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788024605","data":{"timestamp":" 946788024604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakufanikiwa kupata mahali pa kujenga nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788026327","data":{"timestamp":" 946788026326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakufanikiwa kupata mahali pa kujenga nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUFANIKIWA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUFANIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788027293","data":{"timestamp":" 946788027293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakufanikiwa kupata mahali pa kujenga nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPATA"," userResponse":" KUPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788027927","data":{"timestamp":" 946788027927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakufanikiwa kupata mahali pa kujenga nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788028170","data":{"timestamp":" 946788028170"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakufanikiwa kupata mahali pa kujenga nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788029014","data":{"timestamp":" 946788029014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakufanikiwa kupata mahali pa kujenga nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJENGA"," userResponse":" KUJENGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788029819","data":{"timestamp":" 946788029818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakufanikiwa kupata mahali pa kujenga nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788030335","data":{"timestamp":" 946788030335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakufanikiwa kupata mahali pa kujenga nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788030965","data":{"timestamp":" 946788030965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hawakufanikiwa kupata mahali pa kujenga nyumba yao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788033341","data":{"timestamp":" 946788033340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Giza lilipoingia waliamua kukwea mti na kulala pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788034940","data":{"timestamp":" 946788034939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Giza lilipoingia waliamua kukwea mti na kulala pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOINGIA"," userResponse":" LILIPOINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788036388","data":{"timestamp":" 946788036387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Giza lilipoingia waliamua kukwea mti na kulala pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" WALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788037367","data":{"timestamp":" 946788037367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Giza lilipoingia waliamua kukwea mti na kulala pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKWEA"," userResponse":" KUKWEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788038016","data":{"timestamp":" 946788038016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Giza lilipoingia waliamua kukwea mti na kulala pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788038514","data":{"timestamp":" 946788038513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Giza lilipoingia waliamua kukwea mti na kulala pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788039276","data":{"timestamp":" 946788039275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Giza lilipoingia waliamua kukwea mti na kulala pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788039843","data":{"timestamp":" 946788039843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Giza lilipoingia waliamua kukwea mti na kulala pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788043266","data":{"timestamp":" 946788043266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wameshakwea mti huku wakiuvuta mlango baada ya wao waliposikia makelele chini yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788044598","data":{"timestamp":" 946788044597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wameshakwea mti huku wakiuvuta mlango baada ya wao waliposikia makelele chini yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMESHAKWEA"," userResponse":" WAMESHAKWEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788045117","data":{"timestamp":" 946788045116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wameshakwea mti huku wakiuvuta mlango baada ya wao waliposikia makelele chini yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788045258","data":{"timestamp":" 946788045257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wameshakwea mti huku wakiuvuta mlango baada ya wao waliposikia makelele chini yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788046888","data":{"timestamp":" 946788046887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wameshakwea mti huku wakiuvuta mlango baada ya wao waliposikia makelele chini yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIUVUTA"," userResponse":" WAKIUVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788047712","data":{"timestamp":" 946788047712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wameshakwea mti huku wakiuvuta mlango baada ya wao waliposikia makelele chini yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788048678","data":{"timestamp":" 946788048677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wameshakwea mti huku wakiuvuta mlango baada ya wao waliposikia makelele chini yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788048943","data":{"timestamp":" 946788048942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wameshakwea mti huku wakiuvuta mlango baada ya wao waliposikia makelele chini yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788049428","data":{"timestamp":" 946788049428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wameshakwea mti huku wakiuvuta mlango baada ya wao waliposikia makelele chini yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788051284","data":{"timestamp":" 946788051284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wameshakwea mti huku wakiuvuta mlango baada ya wao waliposikia makelele chini yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" WALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788052778","data":{"timestamp":" 946788052777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wameshakwea mti huku wakiuvuta mlango baada ya wao waliposikia makelele chini yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKELELE"," userResponse":" MAKELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788053614","data":{"timestamp":" 946788053614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wameshakwea mti huku wakiuvuta mlango baada ya wao waliposikia makelele chini yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788054006","data":{"timestamp":" 946788054006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wameshakwea mti huku wakiuvuta mlango baada ya wao waliposikia makelele chini yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788057158","data":{"timestamp":" 946788057158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliwaona wanaume sita hatari sana wakiwa na magunia makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWAONA"," userResponse":" WALIWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788057932","data":{"timestamp":" 946788057932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliwaona wanaume sita hatari sana wakiwa na magunia makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788058427","data":{"timestamp":" 946788058427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliwaona wanaume sita hatari sana wakiwa na magunia makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788059661","data":{"timestamp":" 946788059661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliwaona wanaume sita hatari sana wakiwa na magunia makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788060255","data":{"timestamp":" 946788060255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliwaona wanaume sita hatari sana wakiwa na magunia makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788061329","data":{"timestamp":" 946788061328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliwaona wanaume sita hatari sana wakiwa na magunia makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWA"," userResponse":" WAKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788061497","data":{"timestamp":" 946788061496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliwaona wanaume sita hatari sana wakiwa na magunia makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788062376","data":{"timestamp":" 946788062375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliwaona wanaume sita hatari sana wakiwa na magunia makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788063555","data":{"timestamp":" 946788063555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliwaona wanaume sita hatari sana wakiwa na magunia makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788066486","data":{"timestamp":" 946788066485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliogopa sana hata wakauachilia mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" WALIOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788067224","data":{"timestamp":" 946788067223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliogopa sana hata wakauachilia mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788068208","data":{"timestamp":" 946788068208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliogopa sana hata wakauachilia mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788069689","data":{"timestamp":" 946788069688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliogopa sana hata wakauachilia mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAUACHILIA"," userResponse":" WAKAUACHILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788070308","data":{"timestamp":" 946788070307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliogopa sana hata wakauachilia mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788073387","data":{"timestamp":" 946788073386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulianguka chini kwa kishindo na kuwaogofya wale watu hata wakaacha kila kitu na kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIANGUKA"," userResponse":" ULIANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788074089","data":{"timestamp":" 946788074088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulianguka chini kwa kishindo na kuwaogofya wale watu hata wakaacha kila kitu na kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788074360","data":{"timestamp":" 946788074359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulianguka chini kwa kishindo na kuwaogofya wale watu hata wakaacha kila kitu na kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788075481","data":{"timestamp":" 946788075480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulianguka chini kwa kishindo na kuwaogofya wale watu hata wakaacha kila kitu na kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHINDO"," userResponse":" KISHINDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788075550","data":{"timestamp":" 946788075550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulianguka chini kwa kishindo na kuwaogofya wale watu hata wakaacha kila kitu na kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788076820","data":{"timestamp":" 946788076819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulianguka chini kwa kishindo na kuwaogofya wale watu hata wakaacha kila kitu na kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAOGOFYA"," userResponse":" KUWAOGOFYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788077746","data":{"timestamp":" 946788077746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulianguka chini kwa kishindo na kuwaogofya wale watu hata wakaacha kila kitu na kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788078292","data":{"timestamp":" 946788078291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulianguka chini kwa kishindo na kuwaogofya wale watu hata wakaacha kila kitu na kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788079246","data":{"timestamp":" 946788079246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulianguka chini kwa kishindo na kuwaogofya wale watu hata wakaacha kila kitu na kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788080051","data":{"timestamp":" 946788080051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulianguka chini kwa kishindo na kuwaogofya wale watu hata wakaacha kila kitu na kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAACHA"," userResponse":" WAKAACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788080705","data":{"timestamp":" 946788080704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulianguka chini kwa kishindo na kuwaogofya wale watu hata wakaacha kila kitu na kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788081186","data":{"timestamp":" 946788081185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulianguka chini kwa kishindo na kuwaogofya wale watu hata wakaacha kila kitu na kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788081349","data":{"timestamp":" 946788081348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulianguka chini kwa kishindo na kuwaogofya wale watu hata wakaacha kila kitu na kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788082216","data":{"timestamp":" 946788082216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulianguka chini kwa kishindo na kuwaogofya wale watu hata wakaacha kila kitu na kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOROKA"," userResponse":" KUTOROKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788085586","data":{"timestamp":" 946788085585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru na mamake walishuka chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIRUSIRU"," userResponse":" KISIRUSIRU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788085729","data":{"timestamp":" 946788085729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru na mamake walishuka chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788086545","data":{"timestamp":" 946788086545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru na mamake walishuka chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788087429","data":{"timestamp":" 946788087428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru na mamake walishuka chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISHUKA"," userResponse":" WALISHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788088128","data":{"timestamp":" 946788088127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisirusiru na mamake walishuka chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788091421","data":{"timestamp":" 946788091420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofungua yale magunia walipata pesa nguo mablanketi na kila kitu walichohitaji kuanzisha nyumba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFUNGUA"," userResponse":" WALIPOFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788091860","data":{"timestamp":" 946788091859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofungua yale magunia walipata pesa nguo mablanketi na kila kitu walichohitaji kuanzisha nyumba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788092845","data":{"timestamp":" 946788092845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofungua yale magunia walipata pesa nguo mablanketi na kila kitu walichohitaji kuanzisha nyumba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788094190","data":{"timestamp":" 946788094189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofungua yale magunia walipata pesa nguo mablanketi na kila kitu walichohitaji kuanzisha nyumba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPATA"," userResponse":" WALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788095048","data":{"timestamp":" 946788095048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofungua yale magunia walipata pesa nguo mablanketi na kila kitu walichohitaji kuanzisha nyumba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788096136","data":{"timestamp":" 946788096135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofungua yale magunia walipata pesa nguo mablanketi na kila kitu walichohitaji kuanzisha nyumba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788098579","data":{"timestamp":" 946788098579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofungua yale magunia walipata pesa nguo mablanketi na kila kitu walichohitaji kuanzisha nyumba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABLANKETI"," userResponse":" MABLANKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788099211","data":{"timestamp":" 946788099210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofungua yale magunia walipata pesa nguo mablanketi na kila kitu walichohitaji kuanzisha nyumba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788099775","data":{"timestamp":" 946788099774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofungua yale magunia walipata pesa nguo mablanketi na kila kitu walichohitaji kuanzisha nyumba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788100540","data":{"timestamp":" 946788100539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofungua yale magunia walipata pesa nguo mablanketi na kila kitu walichohitaji kuanzisha nyumba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788102220","data":{"timestamp":" 946788102219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofungua yale magunia walipata pesa nguo mablanketi na kila kitu walichohitaji kuanzisha nyumba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHOHITAJI"," userResponse":" WALICHOHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788103401","data":{"timestamp":" 946788103400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofungua yale magunia walipata pesa nguo mablanketi na kila kitu walichohitaji kuanzisha nyumba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZISHA"," userResponse":" KUANZISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788103934","data":{"timestamp":" 946788103934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofungua yale magunia walipata pesa nguo mablanketi na kila kitu walichohitaji kuanzisha nyumba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788104475","data":{"timestamp":" 946788104474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofungua yale magunia walipata pesa nguo mablanketi na kila kitu walichohitaji kuanzisha nyumba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788106923","data":{"timestamp":" 946788106922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788108201","data":{"timestamp":" 946788108201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPATA"," userResponse":" WALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788108981","data":{"timestamp":" 946788108980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788109240","data":{"timestamp":" 946788109240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788109983","data":{"timestamp":" 946788109982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJENGA"," userResponse":" KUJENGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788110615","data":{"timestamp":" 946788110615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788111378","data":{"timestamp":" 946788111377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788112402","data":{"timestamp":" 946788112402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAISHI"," userResponse":" WAKAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788112703","data":{"timestamp":" 946788112702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788113816","data":{"timestamp":" 946788113815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788114749","data":{"timestamp":" 946788114748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788115274","data":{"timestamp":" 946788115274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788115764","data":{"timestamp":" 946788115764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788118295","data":{"timestamp":" 946788118293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788118427","data":{"timestamp":" 946788118427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 8803f619-4154-49ec-873e-934c4ed02ca8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Punde walipata pahali pa kujenga nyumba na wakaishi kwa furaha tangu siku hiyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788152295","data":{"timestamp":" 946788152295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua mazuri yapendeza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788153321","data":{"timestamp":" 946788153320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua mazuri yapendeza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788154866","data":{"timestamp":" 946788154865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua mazuri yapendeza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAPENDEZA"," userResponse":" YAPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788158974","data":{"timestamp":" 946788158974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukiyatazama yanameremeta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIYATAZAMA"," userResponse":" UKIYATAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788160912","data":{"timestamp":" 946788160911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukiyatazama yanameremeta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAMEREMETA"," userResponse":" YANAMEREMETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788164177","data":{"timestamp":" 946788164176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua mazuri yapendeza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788165203","data":{"timestamp":" 946788165202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua mazuri yapendeza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788166754","data":{"timestamp":" 946788166753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua mazuri yapendeza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAPENDEZA"," userResponse":" YAPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788169980","data":{"timestamp":" 946788169979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua mazuri yapendeza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788171007","data":{"timestamp":" 946788171006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua mazuri yapendeza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788172554","data":{"timestamp":" 946788172553"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua mazuri yapendeza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAPENDEZA"," userResponse":" YAPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788176673","data":{"timestamp":" 946788176673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukiyatazama yanameremeta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIYATAZAMA"," userResponse":" UKIYATAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788178596","data":{"timestamp":" 946788178596"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukiyatazama yanameremeta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAMEREMETA"," userResponse":" YANAMEREMETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788181862","data":{"timestamp":" 946788181862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua mazuri yapendeza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788182881","data":{"timestamp":" 946788182881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua mazuri yapendeza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788184415","data":{"timestamp":" 946788184415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua mazuri yapendeza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAPENDEZA"," userResponse":" YAPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788187098","data":{"timestamp":" 946788187098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nzu nzu nzu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZU"," userResponse":" NZU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788187829","data":{"timestamp":" 946788187829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nzu nzu nzu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZU"," userResponse":" NZU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788188203","data":{"timestamp":" 946788188203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nzu nzu nzu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZU"," userResponse":" NZU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788190870","data":{"timestamp":" 946788190869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" We mama nyuki lia we"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WE"," userResponse":" WE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788191272","data":{"timestamp":" 946788191271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" We mama nyuki lia we"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788191785","data":{"timestamp":" 946788191785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" We mama nyuki lia we"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUKI"," userResponse":" NYUKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788192228","data":{"timestamp":" 946788192228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" We mama nyuki lia we"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIA"," userResponse":" LIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788192535","data":{"timestamp":" 946788192535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" We mama nyuki lia we"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WE"," userResponse":" WE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788195400","data":{"timestamp":" 946788195399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Toka mbali kutafuta ua zuri kwa chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOKA"," userResponse":" TOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788195965","data":{"timestamp":" 946788195964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Toka mbali kutafuta ua zuri kwa chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788196884","data":{"timestamp":" 946788196883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Toka mbali kutafuta ua zuri kwa chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788197338","data":{"timestamp":" 946788197337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Toka mbali kutafuta ua zuri kwa chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788197857","data":{"timestamp":" 946788197857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Toka mbali kutafuta ua zuri kwa chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788198096","data":{"timestamp":" 946788198095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Toka mbali kutafuta ua zuri kwa chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788198854","data":{"timestamp":" 946788198853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Toka mbali kutafuta ua zuri kwa chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788201601","data":{"timestamp":" 946788201600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nzu nzu nzu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZU"," userResponse":" NZU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788202342","data":{"timestamp":" 946788202341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nzu nzu nzu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZU"," userResponse":" NZU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788202714","data":{"timestamp":" 946788202714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nzu nzu nzu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZU"," userResponse":" NZU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788205463","data":{"timestamp":" 946788205462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" We mama nyuki lia we"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WE"," userResponse":" WE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788205871","data":{"timestamp":" 946788205871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" We mama nyuki lia we"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788206396","data":{"timestamp":" 946788206396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" We mama nyuki lia we"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUKI"," userResponse":" NYUKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788206853","data":{"timestamp":" 946788206852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" We mama nyuki lia we"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIA"," userResponse":" LIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788207166","data":{"timestamp":" 946788207165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" We mama nyuki lia we"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WE"," userResponse":" WE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Garden_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788209862","data":{"timestamp":" 946788209861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" We mama nyuki lia we"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946788209935","data":{"timestamp":" 946788209935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_055827"," gameId":" 158d9ee4-1eb8-4cba-bca6-acd91e667707"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Garden_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" We mama nyuki lia we"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WE"," userResponse":" WE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}